[
  {
    "text": "US senator seeks US action against AWB",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        2,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        17,
        19,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        35,
        38,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.8978,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Woodside signs big gas deal with Japan",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        8,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        33,
        38,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.8356,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Japanese BSE case compounds US beef fears",
    "entities": [
      [
        9,
        12,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        28,
        30,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.8168,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Govt urged to take its time negotiating China FTA",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        4,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        40,
        45,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.802,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "S Africa begins Iraq kickback inquiry",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        8,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        16,
        20,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7935,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Mr England expects the board of Roberts to endorse the offer at a meeting today.",
    "entities": [
      [
        3,
        10,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        32,
        39,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        74,
        79,
        "DATE"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7801,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Bundaberg Sugar's Mourilyan, Babinda, South Johnstone and Tableland mills all suffered significant damage.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        17,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        18,
        27,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        29,
        36,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        58,
        67,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7641,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The US exported about 500,000 metric tones of wheat to Iraq last marketing year before the UN Volker report on alleged AWB kickbacks to Iraq led to a cut-off of AWB shipments and a surge in US exports.",
    "entities": [
      [
        4,
        6,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        55,
        59,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        60,
        79,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        91,
        93,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        94,
        100,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        136,
        140,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        190,
        192,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7518,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "In Australia, the CSIRO has been working with a group in France trying to isolate the genes responsible for powdery mildew resistance and downey mildew resistance.",
    "entities": [
      [
        3,
        12,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        18,
        23,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        57,
        63,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7391,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The Bundaberg Sugar Company will not open its Mourilyan mill south of Innisfail for this year's cane crush, saying Larry has drastically reduced the harvest forecasts.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        27,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        46,
        55,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        70,
        79,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        89,
        93,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        115,
        120,
        "PER"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7391,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Apple and pear growers have rejected New Zealand's latest bid to export apples to Australia.",
    "entities": [
      [
        37,
        50,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        82,
        91,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7272,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Agriculture group AUSVEG says food labelling laws in Australia are a joke because nobody follows them and enforcement of the rules is non-existent. AUSVEG says consumers are still being fooled into thinking they're buying Australian products because of false or poor labelling.",
    "entities": [
      [
        18,
        24,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        53,
        62,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        148,
        154,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.726,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Mines Minister John Bowler has ruled the land be returned to Rio, resulting in a $75 million loss for Cazaly shareholders on the stock exchange yesterday.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        5,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        15,
        26,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        61,
        64,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        102,
        108,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        144,
        153,
        "DATE"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7259,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Today's National Rural News was broadcast live from the ABARE Outlook conference in Canberra.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        5,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        56,
        69,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        92,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.724,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Just days after asking the Bush administration to probe whether the AWB violated US laws or WTO trade rules, top Senate Agriculture Committee Democrat Tom Harkin has cited US cables first disclosed in the Cole investigation.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        9,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        23,
        46,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        71,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        81,
        83,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        92,
        95,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        113,
        141,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        151,
        161,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        172,
        174,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        205,
        209,
        "PER"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7229,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The Opposition's Gavan O'Connor says the letter was sent in 2002, the same time AWB was paying kickbacks to Iraq though a Jordanian trucking company.",
    "entities": [
      [
        4,
        14,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        17,
        31,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        60,
        64,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        80,
        83,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        108,
        112,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7225,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Industry delegates have met with EU commissioners in Brussels to push Australia's case ahead of world trade talks later this month.",
    "entities": [
      [
        33,
        35,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        53,
        61,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        70,
        79,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        114,
        130,
        "DATE"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7206,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The group also wants AWB sanctioned if it is found to have violated US trade law or World Trade Organisation (WTO) rules.",
    "entities": [
      [
        21,
        24,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        70,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        84,
        108,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        110,
        113,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7167,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The \"Every Family needs a Farmer\" promotion is being run by Agforce and features the Coe family, from Durong, in the state's south.",
    "entities": [
      [
        60,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        85,
        88,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        102,
        108,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.715,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "While Landcare is approaching its 20th anniversary in Victoria, a new survey shows it is not as popular as it used to be.",
    "entities": [
      [
        6,
        14,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        54,
        62,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7108,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Jun 24, 2019 Russia warns of repeat of 1962 Cuban missile crisis. We need to save our oceans. 50 Minutes to Save the World -MUST WATCH- Emmanuel Macron: Trade Wars for Me, But Not for Thee Joe Jonas And Sophie Turner Are Living It Up In Paris Ahead Of Their Wedding Trump imposes new sanctions on Iran, targets supreme leader Trump imposes new sanctions on Iran, targets supreme leader Trump imposes new sanctions on Iran, targets supreme leader Julián Castro can’t catch a break Police violence worsens in Brazil's poor neighbourhoods Google Admits It Wants to ‘Prevent The Next Trump Situation’ Trump imposes new sanctions on Iran, targets supreme leader Trump says he does not need congressional approval to strike Iran Brazil: Bolsonaro Reaffirms His Power over The Demarcation of New Indigenous Territories Stunning giant squid captured on video in US waters for first time Love Island – live: Contestants face shock dumping after Maura turns on Tom over ‘all-mouth’ comment Mexico sends nearly 15,000 troops to the US border Mexico cracks down at US border with 15,000 troops Insider exposes Google’s efforts to influence 2020 election against Trump UBS: World economy ‘one step away from global recession' Mexico deploys 15,000 troops to US border to slow migration Kushner: Israel-Palestine deal won't follow Arab Peace Initiative Mexico’s Crackdown at Its Southern Border, Prompted by Trump, Scares Migrants From Crossing Eerie video captures giant squid in the U.S. for the first time ever Trump appears to name the wrong Iranian leader when announcing sanctions on Iran Greenpeace is calling on West African governments to immediately phase out the wasteful fishmeal and fish oil (FMFO) industry, to stop the threat to regional fish stocks essential for the food security and livelihoods of local people",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        19,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        39,
        43,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        136,
        151,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        189,
        198,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        203,
        216,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        237,
        242,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        266,
        271,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        297,
        301,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        326,
        331,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        357,
        361,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        386,
        391,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        417,
        421,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        446,
        459,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        507,
        513,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        536,
        542,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        580,
        585,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        597,
        602,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        628,
        632,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        657,
        662,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        718,
        722,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        723,
        729,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        731,
        740,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        854,
        856,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        936,
        941,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        951,
        954,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        980,
        986,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1021,
        1023,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1031,
        1037,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1053,
        1055,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1098,
        1104,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1128,
        1132,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1150,
        1155,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1156,
        1159,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1213,
        1219,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1245,
        1247,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1273,
        1280,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1282,
        1288,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1339,
        1345,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1394,
        1399,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1471,
        1475,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1500,
        1505,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1576,
        1580,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1581,
        1591,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7064,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "But Japan's 23rd confirmed BSE case, and the first in beef cattle, may cause even longer odds in that market.",
    "entities": [
      [
        4,
        9,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        27,
        30,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7031,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Members of the United Nations Convention on Biological Diversity, including Australia, banned \"terminator technology\" in 2000, when global protests forced biotech company Monsanto to state it would not commercialise the process.",
    "entities": [
      [
        11,
        64,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        85,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        121,
        125,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        171,
        179,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.702,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The Prime Minister has denied he knew AWB was paying kickbacks to Iraq despite writing to the wheat exporter asking to be kept fully informed on Iraq wheat sales.",
    "entities": [
      [
        38,
        41,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        66,
        70,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        145,
        149,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7017,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The deal was brokered by Trade Minister Mark Vaile, who visited Baghdad in February to save the Iraq wheat trade, after it announced it would no longer deal with monopoly exporter AWB because of the oil-for-food kickbacks scandal.",
    "entities": [
      [
        25,
        30,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        40,
        50,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        64,
        71,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        75,
        83,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        96,
        100,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        180,
        183,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.701,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "AQIS says it is trying to get to obtain more information about the export protocol, but believes it's likely to affect all countries, not just Australia.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        4,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        143,
        152,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.7,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Chief market analyst at Meat and Livestock Australia Peter Weeks says the news will not affect Japan but the latest controversy could delay the resumption of US exports to Korea.",
    "entities": [
      [
        24,
        52,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        53,
        64,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        95,
        100,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        158,
        160,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        172,
        177,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6984,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "It is nearly a month since Trade Minister Mark Vaile told grain growers that AWB would relax its veto power to allow other companies to export to Iraq.",
    "entities": [
      [
        6,
        20,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        27,
        32,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        42,
        52,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        77,
        80,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        146,
        150,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6968,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "The Federal Government has announced plans to improve road train access between central Australia and Queensland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        22,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        88,
        97,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        102,
        112,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6963,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Aug 31, 2019 India declares 1.9m people \"illegal foreigners\" putting them at risk of becoming stateless, as it builds 10 more detention camps Another mass shooting in Texas leaves at least 5 dead, at least10 others injured. Gunman was killed after hijacking multiple vehicles and shooting several, including a police officer Bolsonaro backtracking on decree that banned most fires for land-clearing for 60 days, now saying the ban will only apply to the Amazon region. China has had a rover on the Moon since January. China has had a rover on the moon since January. Texas shootings: Random gun attacks leave five dead Miami RedHawks vs Iowa Hawkeyes - August 31, 2019, on FS1 LIVE NEWS COVERAGE - Odessa Texas mass shooting - Shooter identified as a white male in his mid 30s says the Midland PD. 14 victims says CEO of the Medical Center. Taliban attacks city of Kunduz amid peace talks with US 5 dead, 21 injured in latest mass shooting in Texas, US. Lara face to Alvarez - Boxing, August 31, 2019, on FOX Adorable Baby Is Calling Mummy, Lovely Child Lost Mommy Five killed, including shooter, around 21 injured in Texas shooting British Museum hands over recently-plundered artifacts to Iraq Active shooter in Midland/Odessa TX area. 5 dead and 21 injured migrants now feel more welcome in Canada than usa One suspect dead, one in custody following shooting in Odessa and Midland TEXAS Hong Kong police storm subway with batons as protests rage. Shooter targets people at shopping centers in Odessa and Midland, Texas 2 killed and 20 injuried in Texas mass shooting 'Multiple casualties' in Texas mass shooting Canada, first images from the ship HMS Terror: \"They will reveal details about the tragic Arctic expedition of 1845\" Brazilian citizen data under threat with sale of national tech firms 2 Dead, 20 Injured in West Texas Shooting Spree Mass random shooting in western Texas has left \"multiple gunshot victims\"",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        18,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        167,
        172,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        224,
        230,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        325,
        334,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        403,
        410,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        454,
        460,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        469,
        474,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        498,
        502,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        509,
        516,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        518,
        523,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        558,
        565,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        567,
        572,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        619,
        633,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        637,
        641,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        642,
        650,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        653,
        668,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        673,
        676,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        698,
        704,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        705,
        710,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        769,
        776,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        782,
        796,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        821,
        839,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        841,
        848,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        865,
        871,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        894,
        896,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        943,
        948,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        950,
        952,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        954,
        958,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        967,
        974,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        985,
        1000,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1005,
        1008,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1118,
        1123,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1191,
        1195,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1214,
        1221,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1222,
        1228,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1229,
        1231,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1294,
        1300,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1306,
        1309,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1365,
        1371,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1376,
        1383,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1384,
        1389,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1390,
        1399,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1496,
        1502,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1507,
        1514,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1516,
        1521,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1550,
        1555,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1595,
        1600,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1615,
        1621,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1705,
        1711,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1726,
        1730,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1823,
        1833,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1881,
        1886,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.694,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Sheep producers in the UK have started a Mutton Renaissance Club to improve mutton's image, which could increase Australia's already booming export market.",
    "entities": [
      [
        23,
        25,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        39,
        64,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        82,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        113,
        122,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.694,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Jul 28, 2018 UPSC Combined Geo-Scientist And Geologist exam: Check revised exam pattern, to be effective from 2020 UFC Fight Night: Alvarez vs Poirier 2 - July 28, 2018, at 8 pm ET/5pm PT, Live on Fox, Venue: Scotiabank Saddledome, Calgary, Alberta. CNN  ‘Iran Is Better For America Than Trump’ Scottish government to double funding for breastfeeding Accused Russian agent met with suspected Kremlin spy – POLITICO Trump 2020 campaign denies reports it's producing flags in China Powerful 6.4-magnitude earthquake strikes Indonesia Lebanon sinks tanks in Mediterranean to make new reef Cambodia votes but main opposition absent UFC Fight Night: Alvarez vs Poirier 2 - July 28, 2018, at 8 pm ET/5pm PT, Live on Fox, Venue: Scotiabank Saddledome, Calgary, Alberta. Gen X Women Feel Excluded From Body Positive Movement بـ120 ثانية.. هكذا صنعت \"ناسا\" التاريخ خلال 60 عاما 10 Monstrous Doctors Who Mutilated Their Patients Taiwanese choir bullied by China moves Austrian audience to tears Egypt court sentences 75 to death over 2013 sit-in \"Trump 2020\" Flags Being Made by Factory Workers in China (Photos) &amp;quot;Trump 2020&amp;quot; Flags Being Made by Factory Workers in China (Photos) Alarm grows among Trump officials over lack of cyber defenses An Israeli Arab lawmaker resigned on Saturday and branded the parliament \"racist\" after it passed a controversial new law which declares Israel the nation state of the Jewish people Macron plummets to new poll low after bodyguard scandal that forced him into bizarre denial of gay affair 5 Best Nice Watches for Men: Your Buyer’s Guide (2018) Addiction Consultation Indianapolis | Addiction Recovery Helpline Vatican meets #MeToo: Nuns denounce their abuse by priests DOLPHIN-WHALE HYBRID: RARE NEW SPECIES DISCOVERED OFF HAWAII COAST A Palestinian teen died Saturday of wounds sustained by Israel army fire at a border protest a day earlier, Gaza’s Health Ministry said, as thousands attended the funerals of an 11-year-old boy and a man on crutches also killed in that demonstration.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        17,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        110,
        114,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        132,
        139,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        143,
        150,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        155,
        168,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        197,
        200,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        209,
        230,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        232,
        239,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        241,
        248,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        250,
        253,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        256,
        260,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        275,
        282,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        288,
        293,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        392,
        399,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        406,
        414,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        415,
        420,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        421,
        425,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        474,
        479,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        522,
        531,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        532,
        539,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        555,
        568,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        586,
        594,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        645,
        652,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        656,
        663,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        668,
        681,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        710,
        713,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        745,
        752,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        754,
        761,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        946,
        951,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        985,
        990,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1024,
        1028,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1088,
        1093,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1173,
        1178,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1287,
        1295,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1387,
        1393,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1432,
        1438,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1587,
        1591,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1593,
        1615,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1616,
        1628,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1659,
        1666,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1772,
        1778,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1809,
        1817,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1841,
        1847,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1893,
        1897,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1900,
        1915,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1963,
        1974,
        "DATE"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6939,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "In one of the letters Mr Howard asks AWB managing director Andrew Lindberg to remain in close contact with the Government on Iraq wheat sales.",
    "entities": [
      [
        25,
        31,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        37,
        40,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        59,
        74,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        125,
        129,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6932,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "DPI finds exotic tomato virus in SE Qld",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        3,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        33,
        39,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6929,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "But applications to export more than half a million tonnes of wheat have been before the WEA for weeks, including a Wheat Australia bid to sell 350,000 tonnes to Iraq.",
    "entities": [
      [
        89,
        92,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        97,
        102,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        116,
        131,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        162,
        166,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6928,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Sep 18, 2018 Lana Del Rey’s ‘Venice Bitch’ Is A Shredding Psychedelic Journey Through The Soul 100+ Free Food Stock Photos YouTube will close YouTube Gaming, move it all to the main site FedEx: Amazon’s new delivery service ‘should not be confused as competition’ Machine Gun Kelly called out over Eminem diss, booed while performing ‘Rap Devil’ FedEx: Amazon’s new delivery service ‘should not be confused as competition’ EU ‘ready to improve’ Brexit border offer Yemen conflict: A million more children face famine, NGO warns FedEx: Amazon’s new delivery service ‘should not be confused as competition’ German police launch Europe-wide search for G20 riot suspects: The \"top culprits\" are accused of committing crimes during leftist demonstrations at the Hamburg G20 summit in 2017. It comes as one man was arrested in Hamburg, where police conducted raids relating to the protests When 11 men interrogate: GOP tries to head off Kavanaugh debacle When 11 men interrogate: GOP tries to head off Kavanaugh debacle New China tariff list creates risk of ‘downward cycle’ for US auto industry Dealing with an a***hole at work? This Stanford professor has some tactical advice Herbalife reaches deal with US regulators - BBC News US spares Apple and Fitbit from new China tariffs ICC opens Myanmar Rohingya crimes probe Report: Elton Brand Hired as 76ers GM After Making ‘Strong Impression’ on Owners Massive trove of centuries-old undelivered mail seized by British warships going online When 11 men interrogate: GOP tries to head off Kavanaugh debacle Ethiopia and Eritrea’s second rapprochement People's Vote says 'multiple opportunities' for Brexit referendum China hits back at US with $60bn of new tariffs | Business When 11 men interrogate: GOP tries to head off Kavanaugh debacle In Affront to Those Fleeing US-Backed Wars, Trump Slams Door on Refugees",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        27,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        123,
        130,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        142,
        149,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        187,
        192,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        194,
        200,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        264,
        281,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        298,
        304,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        346,
        351,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        353,
        359,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        423,
        425,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        465,
        470,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        528,
        533,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        535,
        541,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        626,
        632,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        757,
        764,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        779,
        783,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        821,
        828,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        909,
        912,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        931,
        940,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        974,
        977,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        996,
        1005,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1018,
        1023,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1073,
        1075,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1129,
        1137,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1173,
        1182,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1201,
        1203,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1217,
        1225,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1226,
        1228,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1236,
        1241,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1262,
        1267,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1276,
        1279,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1286,
        1293,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1324,
        1335,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1345,
        1350,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1510,
        1513,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1532,
        1541,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1550,
        1558,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1563,
        1570,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1660,
        1665,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1679,
        1681,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1744,
        1747,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1766,
        1775,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1812,
        1814,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1828,
        1833,
        "PER"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6928,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Aug 15, 2019 Conflicts in Hong Kong as student-led protesters and hk police beating student-led volience NFL 2019, August 15, Today's 5 Games Live Stream: Eagles vs Jaguars - at 7:00pm ET. Bengals vs Redskins - at 7:30pm ET. Jets vs Falcons - at 7:30pm ET. Packers vs Ravens - at 7:30pm ET. Raiders vs Cardinals - at 8:00pm ET, on ESPN. US may have supplied tear gas used against Hong Kong protesters The 1975’s Matt Healy Protests Anti-LGBTQ Laws in Dubai by Kissing Male Fan at Show Jair Bolsonaro to Merkel and Norway: Reforest Germany, not Amazon Hong Kong protesters to withdraw all their money from ATMs or change their currency into US Dollars North Korea launches projectiles towards east coast, South Korea says NFL 2019, August 15, Today's 5 Games Live Stream: Eagles vs Jaguars - at 7:00pm ET. Bengals vs Redskins - at 7:30pm ET. Jets vs Falcons - at 7:30pm ET. Packers vs Ravens - at 7:30pm ET. Raiders vs Cardinals - at 8:00pm ET, on ESPN. Go to live- Taiwan sharply boosts defense budget amid China tension North Korea tests 'short-range ballistic missiles' N. Korea fires two unidentified projectiles into East Sea Trump Wants to Buy Greenland Hong Kong protesters plan to withdraw as much money as possible from their banks or change their currency into US dollars, both to protect their own assets and to show the mainland that the semiautonomous island is more than just a cash cow. As Reddit trips over itself to vilify CEOs, it buys, yet again, into the annually reported myth of gross CEO overcompensation. It’s official: July 2019 was Earth’s hottest month on record NFL 2019, August 15, Today's 5 Games Live Stream: Eagles vs Jaguars - 15 at 7:00pm ET. Bengals vs Redskins - at 7:30pm ET. Jets vs Falcons - at 7:30pm ET. Packers vs Ravens - at 7:30pm ET. Raiders vs Cardinals - at 8:00pm ET, on ESPN. Jupiter got slammed by a Uranus-sized planet early in its life, finds new study. Jupiter got slammed by a Uranus-sized planet early in it's life, finds new study. Trump's Green New Deal: President reportedly considering buying Greenland Trump Suggests China’s Xi Meet With Hong Kong Protesters NFL 2019, August 15, Today's 5 Games Live Stream: Eagles vs Jaguars - 15 at 7:00pm ET. Bengals vs Redskins - at 7:30pm ET. Jets vs Falcons - at 7:30pm ET. Packers vs Ravens - at 7:30pm ET. Raiders vs Cardinals - at 8:00pm ET, on ESPN. Go to live- Fast, low and hard to stop: North Korea’s missile tests crank up the threat level Pakistan Rage Over India’s ‘Occupation’ of Kashmir Explodes Into the Streets: ‘I Am Ready to Die’ British Socialite Ghislaine Maxwell spotted at In-N-Out Burger Workers Seize the Shipyard That Built the Titanic, Plan to Make Renewable Energy There",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        26,
        35,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        66,
        68,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        115,
        124,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        126,
        131,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        155,
        161,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        165,
        172,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        189,
        196,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        200,
        208,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        225,
        229,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        233,
        240,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        257,
        264,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        268,
        274,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        291,
        298,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        302,
        311,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        331,
        335,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        337,
        339,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        380,
        389,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        405,
        409,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        412,
        422,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        451,
        456,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        485,
        499,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        503,
        509,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        514,
        520,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        531,
        538,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        551,
        560,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        651,
        662,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        704,
        715,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        731,
        740,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        742,
        747,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        771,
        777,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        781,
        788,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        805,
        812,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        816,
        824,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        841,
        845,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        849,
        856,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        873,
        880,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        884,
        890,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        907,
        914,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        918,
        927,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        947,
        951,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        965,
        971,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1007,
        1012,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1021,
        1032,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1072,
        1080,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1121,
        1129,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1130,
        1135,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1149,
        1158,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1159,
        1168,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1270,
        1272,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1404,
        1410,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1474,
        1482,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1543,
        1552,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1557,
        1562,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1589,
        1597,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1599,
        1608,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1610,
        1615,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1639,
        1645,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1649,
        1656,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1659,
        1661,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1676,
        1683,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1687,
        1695,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1712,
        1716,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1720,
        1727,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1744,
        1751,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1755,
        1761,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1778,
        1785,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1789,
        1798,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1818,
        1822,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1824,
        1831,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1905,
        1912,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1930,
        1936,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1987,
        1992,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2051,
        2060,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2061,
        2066,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2076,
        2081,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2084,
        2086,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2097,
        2106,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2128,
        2137,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        2139,
        2144,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        2168,
        2174,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2178,
        2185,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2205,
        2212,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2216,
        2224,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2241,
        2245,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2249,
        2256,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2273,
        2280,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2284,
        2290,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2307,
        2314,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2318,
        2327,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2347,
        2351,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2393,
        2406,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2447,
        2455,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2466,
        2471,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2490,
        2497,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2563,
        2580,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2592,
        2607,
        "ORG"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6882,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Sep 26, 2019 Philadelphia Eagles anti Green Bay Packers - Sept. 26, 2019 Read: Whistleblower complaint regarding President Trump and Ukraine Eagles to face Packers - 2019 NFL, September 26 Pentagon Letter Undercuts Trump Assertion On Delaying Aid To Ukraine Over Corruption China is killing religious and ethnic minorities and harvesting their organs, UN Human Rights Council told China approves Trump branded spa / escort services Scientific Experiment on Genetically Modified-mosquitoes Goes Wrong, Prompts Backlash Eagles to face Packers - 2019 NFL, September 26 Huawei Mate X Foldable Phone To Go on Sales From October Single, Gay, Italian man adopts girl with Down syndrome who was rejected by her mother, father &amp; 20 other families Eagles to face Packers - 2019 NFL, September 26 Sudan closes borders with Libya and Central Africa Republic EU may be forced to withdraw from nuclear deal, Iran told Pakistani activist who accused army of sexually harassing women flees to US after months in hiding Putin-Linked Mercenaries Are Fighting on Libya’s Front Lines - Mercenaries are assisting Khalifa Haftar’s raid on Tripoli Public outrage over a death penalty handed to a 29-year-old man is spurring Malaysia to start talks to legalise marijuana for medical use, racing to become the first Asian country to do so. Expose The Truth... TEPCO challenged by increasing radioactive water | NHK World In Pakistan’s Thar Desert, Opposition to New Coal Projects Grows Mohammad Bin Salman: Jamal Khashoggi murder 'happened under my watch,' Saudi crown prince tells PBS A Theory of Trump Kompromat Air pollution scientists fired by Trump administration to continue working together to study harmful effects of air quality on health Poll: Most Americans support sending troops, missile defenses to Saudi Arabia Giuliani Won’t Say if He Has a Security Clearance China is trying to control its coal-fuelled electricity, but it's not succeeding",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        32,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        38,
        47,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        48,
        55,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        58,
        72,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        123,
        128,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        133,
        140,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        141,
        147,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        156,
        163,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        166,
        170,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        171,
        174,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        176,
        188,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        189,
        197,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        215,
        220,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        250,
        257,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        274,
        279,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        352,
        375,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        381,
        386,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        396,
        401,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        518,
        524,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        533,
        540,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        543,
        547,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        548,
        551,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        553,
        565,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        566,
        572,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        615,
        622,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        742,
        748,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        757,
        764,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        767,
        771,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        772,
        775,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        777,
        789,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        790,
        795,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        816,
        821,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        826,
        849,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        850,
        852,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        898,
        902,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        981,
        983,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        990,
        996,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1007,
        1012,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1048,
        1053,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1096,
        1112,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1121,
        1128,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1177,
        1188,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1205,
        1213,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1339,
        1344,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1390,
        1393,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1403,
        1411,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1414,
        1425,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1465,
        1484,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1486,
        1501,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1561,
        1564,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1627,
        1632,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1792,
        1804,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1805,
        1813,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1855,
        1860,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6872,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "AWB still has plenty of support among grain growers in central western New South Wales despite the revelations of the Cole inquiry.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        3,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        71,
        86,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        118,
        122,
        "PER"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6872,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Aug 26, 2019 Oklahoma wins case against drugmaker in historic opioid trial (J&amp;J to pay 572 million dollars) Cardinals v Brewers - MLB, August 26, 2019, on ESPN Australian writer Yang Hengjun charged with spying in China Macron slams Bolsonaro for 'disrespectful comments' about his wife UN calls for 'maximum restraint' after alleged Israeli strike in Lebanon | World news Another suspected Israeli strike in Lebanon as war fears intensify Indonesia will move its capital from overcrowded and polluted Jakarta to idyllic rainforest province Emmanuel Macron unveils 20 million euro G7 fund to battle wild fires engulfing the Amazon rainforest Cardinals v Brewers - MLB, August 26, 2019, on ESPN Shocking moment thieves use keyless hack to steal a £90,000 Tesla in 30 seconds MFM now produces the Largest number of First Class Graduates in the World every year - Dr D.K Olukoya G-7 nations pledge $40 million to fight Amazon fires Trump’s fabricated China phone call is ‘a serious escalation of his lying’ which bodes ill for America Effectively Specifying Roof Coatings Based on Facility Needs PewDiePie makes YouTube history and becomes the first solo creator to hit 100 million subscribers Cardinals v Brewers - MLB, August 26, 2019, on ESPN Brazil officials failed to act after warning of 'fire day’ in Amazon, prosecutors say. Investigation into why environment agency ignored warnings that farmers and land-grabbers were planning day of coordinated fires. Calling Prophet Muhammad a pedophile is not protected by free speech, the European Court of Human Rights rules Cardinals v Brewers - MLB, August 26, 2019, on ESPN After reports emerged that U.S. President Donald Trump inquired about the possibility of using nuclear weapons to destroy hurricanes, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) stated that this strategy would be \"devastating.\" Macron states Amazon should be given an international status, if leaders of region take harmful decisions. Hasbro now owns Death Row Records Cardinals v Brewers - MLB, August 26, 2019, on ESPN Amazon fires: Angola and DR Congo 'have more blazes' A woman was required by her husband to choose between him and her dogs, and she chose her dogs",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        21,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        112,
        121,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        124,
        131,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        134,
        137,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        139,
        154,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        159,
        163,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        182,
        194,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        218,
        223,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        224,
        230,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        237,
        246,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        291,
        293,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        356,
        363,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        413,
        420,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        444,
        453,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        506,
        513,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        545,
        560,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        585,
        587,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        628,
        634,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        646,
        655,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        658,
        665,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        668,
        671,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        673,
        688,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        693,
        697,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        758,
        763,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        778,
        781,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        852,
        862,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        868,
        879,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        920,
        926,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        933,
        938,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        952,
        957,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1028,
        1035,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1097,
        1106,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1113,
        1120,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1195,
        1204,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1207,
        1214,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1217,
        1220,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1222,
        1237,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1242,
        1246,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1247,
        1253,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1309,
        1315,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1438,
        1441,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1472,
        1488,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1534,
        1568,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1575,
        1584,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1587,
        1594,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1597,
        1600,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1602,
        1617,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1622,
        1626,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1654,
        1658,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1669,
        1681,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1761,
        1812,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1814,
        1818,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1870,
        1876,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1884,
        1890,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1977,
        1983,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1993,
        2002,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2011,
        2020,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2023,
        2030,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2033,
        2036,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2038,
        2053,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        2058,
        2062,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2063,
        2069,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2077,
        2083,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2088,
        2096,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6852,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Potato growers in Victoria are facing a 10 per cent supply cut and lower prices from food processor McCain this year.",
    "entities": [
      [
        18,
        26,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        100,
        106,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        107,
        116,
        "DATE"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6851,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Iraq market",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        4,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6847,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Oct 14, 2019 Assad Forces Surge Forward in Syria as U.S. Pulls Back Nicola Sturgeon to attack 'so-called strongman leaders'. SNP leader’s conference speech will oppose ‘crude populism’ of Johnson and Trump Iranian women cheer at soccer game, finally England's Euro 2020 qualifier in Bulgaria was twice halted in the first-half due to racist chanting in Sofia ‘The Internal Silence Is Deafening,’ Blizzard Employee Says About China Controversy Ecuador protests come to an end as deal is reached on fuel subsidies Fourteen police dead in Mexico gun ambush Trump imposes sanctions on Turkey over its incursion into Syria France jails women for failed Notre Dame car bombing: report NFL news and notes: Bucs won't bench Winston, Cooper has 'painful' thigh bruise Gordon Sondland, U.S. ambassador to the EU and a key figure in Ukraine scandal, long coveted ambassadorship Federal prosecutors probing Giuliani’s business dealings in Ukraine President Xi Jinping vows Chinese separatists will be ‘smashed to pieces’ as US-themed protests begin in Hong Kong Trump makes 'insane' suggestion Kurds are deliberately freeing Isis prisoners in Syria Venezuela destroying the Brazilian beaches with oil. 2000 km of oil on Brazilian beaches. The oil is from Venezuela. Here in Brazil i ´m not listening France blaming Venezuela. United Nations? European Media? Really sad. With Turkey’s invasion of Syria, concerns mount over nukes at Incirlik Facebook paid just £28m tax after record £1.6bn revenues in UK | Technology | The Guardian Top U.S. Republican says Trump's sanctions on Turkey 'do not go far enough' - Reuters Libra, criptomoeda do Facebook, sofre com debandada de parceiros EU governments limit arms sales to Turkey but avoid embargo - Reuters Catalonia's Puigdemont calls prison sentences for separatist leaders an 'atrocity' - Reuters Lions Attack Anti Packers - 2019 NFL, October 14 Trump Announces Sanctions Against Turkey, Also Himself PROJECT VERITAS VIDEO: CNN Head Appears To Admit Network Pushing Impeachment, Has ‘Personal Vendetta Against Trump,’ Employee Says Russia announces massive trans-Arctic nuclear war games",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        18,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        43,
        48,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        52,
        56,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        68,
        83,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        125,
        128,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        188,
        195,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        200,
        205,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        250,
        257,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        283,
        291,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        353,
        358,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        425,
        430,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        443,
        450,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        536,
        542,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        554,
        559,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        581,
        587,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        612,
        617,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        618,
        624,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        679,
        682,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        699,
        703,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        716,
        723,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        725,
        731,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        759,
        774,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        776,
        780,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        799,
        801,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        822,
        829,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        895,
        903,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        927,
        934,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        945,
        955,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1012,
        1014,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1040,
        1049,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1050,
        1055,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1113,
        1117,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1131,
        1136,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1137,
        1146,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1243,
        1252,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1262,
        1268,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1288,
        1294,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1303,
        1312,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1314,
        1328,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1363,
        1369,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1384,
        1389,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1420,
        1428,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1429,
        1437,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1489,
        1491,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1507,
        1519,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1524,
        1528,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1545,
        1550,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1566,
        1572,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1598,
        1605,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1606,
        1611,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1628,
        1636,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1671,
        1673,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1706,
        1712,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1733,
        1740,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1741,
        1750,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1753,
        1763,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1826,
        1833,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1862,
        1866,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1872,
        1882,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1883,
        1888,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1917,
        1923,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1961,
        1964,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2047,
        2052,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2069,
        2075,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.684,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Sep 14, 2018 Meet Kylie Rogers, the woman behind the AFL’s bold (and risky) growth push Plea deal exposes Paul Manafort as bare-knuckled political operative One of the most popular Ethereum apps sure looks like a Ponzi scheme Singapore's Mandai eco-resort: Paving paradise to put up an eco-resort Alex Jones’ 5 most disturbing and ridiculous conspiracy theories Ariana Grande shares a heartbreaking tribute to Mac Miller Alex Jones’ 5 most disturbing and ridiculous conspiracy theories Manafort’s surrender shows Mueller probe’s overwhelming force Plea deal exposes Paul Manafort as bare-knuckled political operative Meet Kylie Rogers, the woman behind the AFL’s bold (and risky) growth push Western Europe on swine fever alert as Belgium sees wild boar cases Brazil’s Pankararu finally win land rights, but fight isn’t over Russia reportedly warned Mattis it could use nuclear weapons in Europe, and it made him see Moscow as an 'existential threat' to the US ‘There never is a strategy’: Trump confronts twin Manafort and Kavanaugh crises Desperate for cash, Venezuela threatens to sue its neighbors ‘There never is a strategy’: Trump confronts twin Manafort and Kavanaugh crises Strawberry contamination prompts $100,000 reward for information Meet Kylie Rogers, the woman behind the AFL’s bold (and risky) growth push Brazil’s Pankararu finally win land rights, but fight isn’t over Manafort Conspired With Israeli Official To Influence Obama’s Ukraine Policy, Mueller Documents Show Russia's largest-ever war games and NATO concerns US 'brute' of a storm turns deadly Meet Kylie Rogers, the woman behind the AFL’s bold (and risky) growth push Aaron Judge to Be Activated by Yankees; Hit DL with Wrist Injury in July Russia reportedly warned Mattis it could use nuclear weapons in Europe, and it made him see Moscow as an 'existential threat' to the US",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        18,
        30,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        53,
        56,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        88,
        92,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        106,
        119,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        181,
        189,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        226,
        235,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        238,
        244,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        297,
        308,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        362,
        375,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        410,
        420,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        421,
        432,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        486,
        494,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        513,
        520,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        548,
        552,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        566,
        579,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        622,
        634,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        657,
        660,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        692,
        706,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        731,
        738,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        760,
        766,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        769,
        778,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        825,
        831,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        850,
        856,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        889,
        895,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        917,
        923,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        958,
        960,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        990,
        995,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1011,
        1019,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1024,
        1033,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1061,
        1070,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1131,
        1136,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1152,
        1160,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1165,
        1174,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1252,
        1264,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1287,
        1290,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1322,
        1328,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1331,
        1340,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1441,
        1446,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1449,
        1456,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1465,
        1472,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1488,
        1494,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1524,
        1528,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1538,
        1540,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1578,
        1590,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1613,
        1616,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1648,
        1659,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1679,
        1686,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1716,
        1720,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1721,
        1727,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1746,
        1752,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1785,
        1791,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1813,
        1819,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1854,
        1856,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6831,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Oct 02, 2018 North Korea and Public Opinion FBI's Kavanaugh investigation may wrap up as soon as Wednesday Russia claims it has killed 85,000 terrorists and zero civilians in Syria Ciprofloxacin, a common antibiotic, changes mitochondrial DNA, impairs mitochondrial energy production and blocks cellular growth differentiation Malaysias PM calls Jews hook-nosed Will having more women in US Congress change anything? The double lives of vulnerable House Republicans \"I fear American politics will continue to reflect profound disappointment in teachers, and teachers themselves will continue to feel embattled.\" -The Teacher Wars @DanaGoldstein Russia claims it has killed 85,000 terrorists and zero civilians in Syria US threatens preemptive strike on Russian nuclear missiles Trump administration working to weaken EPA radiation regulations Grassley Releases Bizarre Letter From Former Weatherman To Undermine Kavanaugh Accuser Trump on sexual assault claims: ‘It’s a very scary time for young men in America’ Trump engaged in tax fraud, dubious schemes in 1990s: NYT Buying or Selling Top Teams as College Football Playoff Contenders Will having more women in US Congress change anything? In only four countries does a majority have confidence in how Trump approaches world | The Star Having acne in high school is positively correlated with a high GPA and successful university completion: study Jolyon Palmer column: Why Mercedes were right to use team orders Brazil poll shows far-right Bolsonaro beating leftist in run-off Loving Pablo is a violent, soapy melodrama elevated by movie stars: EW review Brazil poll shows far-right Bolsonaro breathing leftist in run-off Kavanaugh’s 1983 Letter Offers Inside Look at High School Clique Bangladesh Delays Plans to Move Rohingya Refugees to Flood-Prone Island Taiwan Is Becoming A Top Destination For Artificial Intelligence In Asia | Artificial brains threaten to outnumber real ones in Taiwan, as the island's prowess in AI continues to grow",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        13,
        24,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        44,
        47,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        50,
        59,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        97,
        106,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        107,
        113,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        175,
        180,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        388,
        390,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        391,
        399,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        448,
        453,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        645,
        651,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        713,
        718,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        719,
        721,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        778,
        783,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        817,
        820,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        843,
        851,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        912,
        921,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        930,
        935,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1003,
        1010,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1012,
        1017,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1059,
        1064,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1066,
        1069,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1163,
        1165,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1166,
        1174,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1254,
        1259,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1279,
        1287,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1400,
        1413,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1426,
        1434,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1465,
        1471,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1493,
        1502,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1598,
        1600,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1608,
        1614,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1636,
        1645,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1675,
        1684,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1687,
        1691,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1740,
        1750,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1812,
        1818,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1880,
        1884,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1940,
        1946,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6826,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Sep 22, 2019 Hundreds of people have held a high-altitude “funeral” for a Swiss glacier that has been lost to global warming. Climate activists dressed in black clothes climbed to 2,600 metres above sea level to pay their respects to the last remnants of the Pizol glacier in the Glarus Alps, east Switzerland. Israel’s Arab parties reluctantly back Benny Gantz for PM, but push is still on for unity government Browns face to Rams - September 22, 2019 Indonesian investigators determine 737 MAX design flaw and oversight lapses in Lion Air crash: WSJ ZEvent french caritative stream collect 3.5 million euros for Pastor Institut in only a weekend Rams athwart Browns - 2019 NFL, Sep 22 on NBC ZEvent french caritative stream collect 3.5 million Trump admits he discussed Biden in call with Ukrainian president Trump admits to discussing Biden in scrutinized talk with Ukrainian leader Browns face to Rams - September 22, 2019 Browns face to Rams - September 22, 2019 Philippines launches polio vaccine campaign after new outbreak French streamers just raised more than 3.5 million euros ($3.9M) towards the Pasteur Institute (Vaccines/Cancer/Rare illnessses research) in the biggest charity stream ever. Greek police arrest Syrian migrants posing as volleyball team at Athens airport Rams athwart Browns - 2019 NFL, Sep 22 on NBC Indonesian investigators determine 737 MAX design flaw and oversight lapses in Lion Air crash - WSJ Browns face to Rams - September 22, 2019 Rescue hopes fade as Thomas Cook slides towards collapse Iran asks West to leave Persian Gulf as tensions heightened Make climate fight 'sexy,' says Japan's new environment minister Britain to create 1 billion pound fund for clean energy technology General Jewish migration. Netblocks.org confirms Facebook Messenger, BBC News and social media CDN servers restriction in Egypt by leading providers amid demonstrations against government corruption A Crackdown on Islam Is Spreading Across China Lindsey Graham says Department of Justice should look at the Biden-Ukraine connection",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        259,
        264,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        276,
        291,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        298,
        309,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        311,
        317,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        350,
        361,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        412,
        418,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        427,
        431,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        434,
        452,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        532,
        540,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        548,
        551,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        614,
        629,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        633,
        647,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        648,
        652,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        661,
        667,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        670,
        674,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        680,
        686,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        690,
        693,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        694,
        700,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        746,
        751,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        772,
        777,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        811,
        816,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        838,
        843,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        886,
        892,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        901,
        905,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        908,
        926,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        927,
        933,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        942,
        946,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        949,
        967,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        968,
        979,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1104,
        1125,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1270,
        1276,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1285,
        1289,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1298,
        1304,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1307,
        1311,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1317,
        1323,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1327,
        1330,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1410,
        1418,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1427,
        1430,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1431,
        1437,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1446,
        1450,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1453,
        1471,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1493,
        1504,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1529,
        1533,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1539,
        1543,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1553,
        1565,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1621,
        1626,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1654,
        1661,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1747,
        1760,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1770,
        1778,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1790,
        1798,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1843,
        1848,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1961,
        1966,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1967,
        1981,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1987,
        2008,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2028,
        2033,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2034,
        2041,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6826,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Feb 23, 2019 ‘Hypocrite’ priests enabled abuse crisis and church hid secret files, Vatican told Health expert warns of 12,000 heat deaths a year in Spain without climate change action | Around 12,000 people could die every year from excessive heat by 2050, up from about 1,400 currently, unless action is taken on climate change, according to a health expert Climate change forces low-lying Marshall Islands to 'elevate islands' | The far-flung Marshall Islands needs to raise its islands if it is to avoid being drowned by rising sea levels, President Hilda Heine has warned Dem chairmen demand Barr release Mueller report Namibian lawmakers seek justice from Germany on genocide: A delegation of Namibian lawmakers is in Berlin to vigorously push for an agreement with Germany on the genocide it committed against the Nama and Herero people of Namibia more than 100 years ago North Korea’s Kim reported en route to Vietnam summit with Trump DeGale v Eubank Jr build-up &amp; Selby undercard fight North Korea’s Kim reported en route to Vietnam summit with Trump Judge dismisses charges in 10-year-old boy’s decapitation on Kansas waterslide Dirrell vs. Yildirim (Main event)- Boxing, February 23, 2019, at 10 pm ET/7 pm PT, Live on FS1, Venue: Minneapolis Armory, Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA. There’s a formula to winning the Oscars, and it’s all in the statistics DeGale v Eubank Jr build-up &amp; Selby undercard fight North Korea’s Kim reported en route to Vietnam summit with Trump Grace wears a red light bucket on her head for 40 minutes a day — she says it improves her life Dem chairmen demand Barr release Mueller report Live: Duke Taking on Syracuse Without Zion Which NBA Teams Have the Best Young Cores? Alex Bregman Wants It All Which NBA Teams Have the Best Young Cores? North Korea’s Kim reported en route to Vietnam summit with Trump Grace wears a red light bucket on her head for 40 minutes a day — she says it improves her life Aid arrives in Venezuela, as soldiers smash border barricade to defect | CBC News [unable to retrieve full-text content]http://feeds.gossiponthis.com/~r/gossiponthis/~3/RR1O1Ecf4dM/ The post R. Kelly’s Mugshot Released by Chicago Police After He’s Booked on Sex Abuse Charges appeared first on My style by Kartia. North Korea’s Kim reported en route to Vietnam summit with Trump Dirrell vs. Yildirim (Main event)- Boxing, February 23, 2019, at 10 pm ET/7 pm PT, Live on FS1, Venue: Minneapolis Armory, Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        83,
        90,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        148,
        153,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        251,
        255,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        391,
        407,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        445,
        461,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        553,
        564,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        596,
        600,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        609,
        616,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        661,
        668,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        723,
        729,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        771,
        778,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        829,
        835,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        846,
        853,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        854,
        877,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        878,
        891,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        892,
        895,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        917,
        924,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        937,
        942,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        943,
        949,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        952,
        961,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        977,
        982,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        999,
        1012,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1013,
        1016,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1038,
        1045,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1058,
        1063,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1091,
        1102,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1125,
        1131,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1143,
        1150,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1155,
        1163,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1186,
        1203,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1234,
        1237,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1266,
        1277,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1279,
        1288,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1290,
        1293,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1367,
        1373,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1376,
        1385,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1401,
        1406,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1423,
        1436,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1437,
        1440,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1462,
        1469,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1482,
        1487,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1488,
        1493,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1604,
        1608,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1617,
        1624,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1638,
        1642,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1653,
        1661,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1670,
        1674,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1681,
        1684,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1718,
        1730,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1750,
        1753,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1787,
        1800,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1801,
        1804,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1826,
        1833,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1846,
        1851,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1852,
        1857,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1948,
        1951,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1963,
        1972,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2021,
        2029,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2139,
        2149,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2170,
        2177,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2242,
        2250,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2254,
        2260,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2262,
        2275,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2276,
        2279,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2301,
        2308,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2321,
        2326,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2327,
        2334,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2339,
        2347,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2370,
        2387,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        2418,
        2421,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2450,
        2461,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2463,
        2472,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2474,
        2477,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6821,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Oct 09, 2019 The EU could delay Brexit until next summer to allow second referendum Turkey opens ground assault on Syria's Kurds (US allies in the fight against ISIS) ; U.S. Republicans turn on Trump Johnson &amp; Johnson ordered to pay $8bn to man who 'developed female breast tissue' 23 Ways To Make Long Flights Less Miserable Trump not worried about Isis fighters fleeing Syria because ‘they’re going to be escaping to Europe’ Bushfires break out across Australia, destroy homes - Nearly 30 homes have been destroyed in bushfires which intensified in parts of Australia Seminary teacher arrested in Kabirwala(Pakistan) for alleged rape of teenage boy Ukrainian MP Press Conference: Biden Paid $900k by Burisma Blizzard Employees Staged a Walkout to Protest Banned Pro-Hong Kong Gamer sisi is using the country resources to fight his opposition in an illegal way and violating human rights. Everyone is so alarmed by the US leaving Northern Syria but Turkey has voiced concerns about arming the YPG Kurdish Militias, that they consider to be terrorist, for years. It just never made the news. The US supported the YPG knowing that they have substantial ties to the PKK. Mexico will legalise cannabis this month Trump defends Syria move: The Kurds 'didn't help us' in Normandy Pence Aiming to Release Records of His Own Ukraine Calls Fleeing civilians tell CNN they don't know where to go As Turkey starts to invade Northern Syria Rudy Giuliani serves himself and private businesses while talking for Trump Abrar Fahad killing: Bangladesh student was beaten for four hours Ecuador Protests Enter 7th Day Against Pro-IMF Economic Reforms UK says has serious concerns over Turkish offensive in Syria Jennifer Griffin: \"I just spoke to a distraught US Special Forces soldier who is among the 1000 or so US troops in Syria tonight who is serving alongside the SDF Kurdish forces. It was one of the hardest phone calls I have ever taken.\" | \"I am ashamed for the first time in my career.\" [Thread] Trump addresses reporter as 'Mr Kurd' Senators draft bipartisan sanctions bill over Turkey's assault on Kurds Greek Parliamenter Angelos Syrigos from NDP Calls for a War against Turkey Erik Prince's company plans business in China province under human rights scrutiny according to financial disclosure Blizzard employees staged a walkout after the company banned a Hong Kong gamer for pro-Hong Kong views",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        17,
        19,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        45,
        56,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        84,
        90,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        115,
        120,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        130,
        132,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        161,
        165,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        169,
        173,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        194,
        199,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        200,
        207,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        214,
        221,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        330,
        335,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        354,
        358,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        376,
        381,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        423,
        429,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        458,
        467,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        564,
        573,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        603,
        621,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        686,
        691,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        706,
        722,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        788,
        792,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        924,
        926,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        935,
        949,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        954,
        960,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        998,
        1001,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1060,
        1065,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1100,
        1102,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1117,
        1120,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1168,
        1171,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1173,
        1179,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1203,
        1213,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1214,
        1219,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1228,
        1233,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1270,
        1278,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1279,
        1284,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1322,
        1329,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1359,
        1362,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1394,
        1400,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1418,
        1432,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1433,
        1446,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1503,
        1508,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1509,
        1520,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1530,
        1540,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1575,
        1582,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1598,
        1605,
        "DATE"
      ],
      [
        1614,
        1621,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1639,
        1641,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1694,
        1699,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1700,
        1716,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        1748,
        1750,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1751,
        1765,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1802,
        1804,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1815,
        1820,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        1858,
        1861,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        1995,
        2000,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2027,
        2031,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2079,
        2085,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2124,
        2139,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2145,
        2148,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2173,
        2179,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2180,
        2193,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        2220,
        2225,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        2297,
        2305,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        2360,
        2369,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6799,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Palandri's Gordon Grant says WA is being recognised as producing a unique, quality wine for under $24.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        8,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        11,
        23,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        29,
        31,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6798,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  },
  {
    "text": "Tanholm Limousin stud owner Kjedl Sorenson, from the Darling Downs in Queensland, says the sale has attracted interest from across Australia.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        16,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        28,
        42,
        "PER"
      ],
      [
        49,
        66,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        70,
        80,
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        131,
        140,
        "LOC"
      ]
    ],
    "uncertainty": 0.6797,
    "verified": true,
    "was_edited": false
  }
]