[
  [
    "Chris Barnard from Arafura Pearls, north of Nhulunbuy says it is a lucky escape.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          19,
          33,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          44,
          53,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Blocked-off streets, bag searches and sniffer dogs greeted those who entered court two on level five of the building ahead of the Prime Minister's long-awaited appearance at the Cole inquiry.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          178,
          182,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "An invasive aquatic weed is proving extremely hard to eradicate from the Northern Territory.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          69,
          91,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jun 18, 2018 Elon Musk calls out sabotage by disgruntled employee Taliban fighters anger leaders after taking selfies with Afghan troops during ceasefire Best Webcam for Streaming | Top 7 Picks &amp; Buyer’s Guide 'How is this not child abuse?': Homeland Security secretary gets mercilessly grilled over family separation policy in heated press briefing Dr. Dre is working on a movie about the late singer Marvin Gaye, Selection has discovered. The rapper, whose movie credit embrace 2015’s “Straight Outta Compton,” on which he served as a producer and an inspiration for the movie, is within the early phases of getting the venture off the bottom. A Ex-Philippine dictator Ferdinand Marcos was given a hero's burial with military honours, a deeply controversial move three decades after he was ousted in a \"People Power\" revolution Israel moves to ban filming soldiers after controversial videos Canada tracking Trump's border crackdown to see if U.S. remains safe for asylum seekers Report says over 1 billion small arms in world, up from 2007 Trump threatens to hit China with new tariffs on $200 billion in goods Ted Cruz to introduce first GOP bill solving child separation Rapper XXXTENTACION dead at 20 in Broward County Trump says he has asked USTR to identify $200 billion in Chinese goods for additional tariffs at 10% rate One in three teachers are providing pupils with basic hygiene products such as toothpaste and soap amid soaring child poverty rates, a new study shows. 'I didn’t come into the profession to see children suffer,' says head teacher. N.Korea Offers to Remove Long-Range Artillery from Frontline - The Chosun Ilbo (English Edition): Daily News from Korea Trump says he has asked USTR to identify $200 billion in Chinese goods for additional tariffs at 10% rate Rapper XXXTentacion Shot Dead at Age 20 US calls on Russia to release 'unjustly' jailed political and religious prisoners Libya's coast guard recovers five bodies from migrant boat Rapper XXXTentacion is lifeless after being shot in Miami, Florida. Not too lengthy after it was confirmed that XXX had died, members of the Hip Hop neighborhood, together with rappers Kanye West and J. Cole, took to social media to provide tributes. “Relaxation in peace,” Kanye wrote. “I by no m Ex-Israeli minister charged with spying for Iran Libya's coast guard recovers five bodies from migrant boat Federal judge approved landmark deal to compensate members of military and other agencies who were investigated and sometimes fired because of their sexual orientation. Cheers of joy and celebratory hugs greeted decision after hours of testimony today from class action members. Rapper XXXTentacion dead at 20 after shooting Pentagon says it's 'suspended all planning' for military exercise with South Korea.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          22,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          66,
          73,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          246,
          263,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          354,
          361,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          406,
          417,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          419,
          428,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          484,
          488,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          675,
          691,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          769,
          782,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          834,
          840,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          898,
          904,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          914,
          919,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          949,
          953,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1042,
          1046,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1047,
          1052,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1070,
          1075,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1118,
          1126,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1146,
          1149,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1187,
          1199,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1214,
          1228,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1229,
          1234,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1253,
          1257,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1566,
          1573,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1629,
          1644,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1680,
          1685,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1686,
          1691,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1710,
          1714,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1799,
          1811,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1825,
          1831,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1832,
          1834,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1844,
          1850,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1914,
          1919,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1980,
          1992,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2025,
          2030,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2032,
          2039,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2085,
          2088,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2158,
          2168,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2173,
          2180,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2247,
          2252,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2315,
          2319,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2320,
          2325,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2625,
          2630,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2665,
          2677,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2686,
          2688,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2704,
          2712,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2775,
          2786,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jun 21, 2018 Chinese figure skating judges banned for bias at Pyeongchang Olympics American tourist raped near Trafalgar Square in London The 50 Best Weightlifting Shoes 2018 Trump Campaign Data Firm Got Hacked Clinton Emails ‘A Month’ Before Wikileaks, Mueller May Know, Report Says: A bombshell report by a BBC correspondent claims that Cambridge Analytica came into possession of hacked Democratic emails at least a month before Wikileaks dumped them online. Trump Campaign Data Firm Got Hacked Clinton Emails ‘A Month’ Before Wikileaks, Mueller May Know, Report Says: A bombshell report by a BBC correspondent claims that Cambridge Analytica came into possession of hacked Democratic emails at least a month before Wikileaks dumped them online. Iranian women watched the World Cup in a stadium for the first time in nearly 40 years Donald Trump signs order ending family separations at border First lady Melania Trump wore a jacket with the phrase \"I really don't care, do u?\" scrawled across the back to board her flight to Texas. Watchdog expected to find Vote Leave broke rules 'Moral panic' over gaming disorder listing Best Tanning Oil Reviews and Tan Guide for your Beautiful Glow American whiskey makers face dreaded reality: Tariffs Saudi Arabia will spend $750 million to build a 37-mile-long canal which would transform its Gulf rival Qatar from a peninsula into an island Canada housing non-profit courts Ottawa with affordability plan – as founder Westbank woos millionaires in China with gifts and soaring prices Vietnam arrests more oil executives amid corruption crackdown Cambodia’s Royalist Party Demands Probe of Crash That Left Prince Injured, Princess Dead How China could hit the U.S. where it hurts Oxfam Caught In Haitian Pay for Sex Scandal North Korea blowing up test sites, 'total denuclearisation' started: Trump Foster mom on trauma of separated migrant children: 'They are coming crying, almost hysterical' Germany’s Merkel calls for solutions to Iran’s “aggressive tendencies” Botvac D7 vs Shark ION 750: Which is Best for You? Charges dropped against 17 migrants with children, a potential shift in Trump's zero tolerance policy Italian art sleuths 'discover Leonardo da Vinci's earliest masterpiece,' complete with tiny signature: Italian scholars claim to have discovered the earliest known work by Leonardo da Vinci – a previously unattributed portrait of the Archangel Gabriel. CO2 crisis: Shops and pubs could start running out of some food and drink items as soon as this weekend, as Ministers are poised to intervene to help businesses.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          131,
          137,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          170,
          174,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          175,
          180,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          211,
          218,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          243,
          252,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          254,
          261,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          309,
          312,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          339,
          358,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          408,
          424,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          432,
          441,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          462,
          467,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          498,
          505,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          530,
          539,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          541,
          548,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          596,
          599,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          626,
          645,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          695,
          711,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          719,
          728,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          820,
          835,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          836,
          848,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          908,
          921,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1029,
          1034,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1245,
          1257,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1338,
          1342,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1349,
          1354,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1387,
          1393,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1420,
          1426,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1464,
          1472,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1494,
          1499,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1530,
          1537,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1592,
          1600,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1685,
          1690,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1705,
          1709,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1725,
          1730,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1769,
          1780,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1838,
          1843,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1940,
          1947,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1950,
          1956,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1980,
          1984,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2134,
          2139,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2194,
          2213,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2336,
          2353,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2394,
          2415,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2508,
          2520,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "May 15, 2018 Why are businesses aiming to improve customer experience? Trump supporter destroyed and dealt with this leftist senator N. Korea does NOT cancel talks with US. They postpone talks with S. Korea and warn US about its behavior. Nasrallah Says Golan Attack Tells Israel Its Raids Won't Go Unpunished MH370 Experts Think They've Finally Solved The Mystery Of The Doomed Malaysia Airlines Flight The official statement from North Korea about “Max Thunder” and the NK-US relations. The Best Water Purification For Your Car’s Emergency Kit N. Korea reportedly threatens to pull out of U.S. summit over military exercises Putin inaugurates controversial bridge by driving a truck across to seized peninsula Crimea. The 12-mile-long bridge that spans the Kerch Strait establishes Russia’s first land connection with Crimea. Georgian techno fans and extremists clash in Tbilisi in fight for club culture Xi stresses centralized, unified leadership of CPC Central Committee over foreign affairs - Xinhua Turkey to receive F-35 fighters despite US senators objection - Xinhua New Alberta parks create world’s largest boreal forest preserve: government N. Korea reportedly threatens to pull out of U.S. summit over military exercises Start your engines: Putin driving truck, opens newly-built Crimean Bridge Is this Not An Amazing? This pilot is about to board a moving ship Putin drives truck over new controversial bridge linking Russia to Crimea peninsula Canadian physician Tarek Loubani shot in Gaza Strip while providing medical care Uganda Gov't Imposes New Tax On Bibles And Qurans North Korea warns US as it suspends South Korea talks over military drills Justice Department and F.B.I. Are Investigating Cambridge Analytica 39 Short Hairstyles for Round Faces You Can Rock! Who's fault is it? Palestinian envoy recalled from Washington over Israeli embassy move Taiwan President visits new offices of U.S. American Institute in Taiwan",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          71,
          76,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          133,
          141,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          169,
          171,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          198,
          206,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          216,
          218,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          239,
          248,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          254,
          259,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          273,
          279,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          379,
          396,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          432,
          443,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          472,
          474,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          546,
          554,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          591,
          595,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          627,
          632,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          712,
          718,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          755,
          771,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          784,
          790,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          820,
          826,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          873,
          880,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          907,
          909,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          954,
          975,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1006,
          1012,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1046,
          1048,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1081,
          1088,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1153,
          1161,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1198,
          1202,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1254,
          1259,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1375,
          1380,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1432,
          1438,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1442,
          1448,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1478,
          1491,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1500,
          1510,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1540,
          1546,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1590,
          1601,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1608,
          1610,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1626,
          1637,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1665,
          1683,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1688,
          1694,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1713,
          1732,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1834,
          1844,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1871,
          1877,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1910,
          1933,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1937,
          1943,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "\"The device works by having some electronic sensors that are picking up chemicals that are part of an odour and that creates an electrical signal that can be picked up by a computer and could be relayed to the farm office,\" Dr Colditz said.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          227,
          234,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Meanwhile the US is ramping up pressure on Australia's single desk for wheat exports, as Federal Government ministers begin appearing before the Cole inquiry.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          14,
          16,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          43,
          52,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          89,
          107,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          145,
          149,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "New strains of stem rust disease found in SA",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          42,
          44,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The top price for the day of $880 a head went to Ellendale graziers Greg and Tania Downham for their Hereford-Charolais steers.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          18,
          25,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          49,
          58,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          68,
          72,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          77,
          90,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jun 30, 2018 Japanese Private Rocket Launch fails (Video) Giuliani Promises Exiles Trump Will Bring Down Iran Regime \"Hordes of illegal Muslim immigrants are coming in to Islamise the country.\" South Korea to tighten Asylum laws, turn away 500 Yemeni asylum seekers after public backlash against sudden influx of migrant arrivals. Belgian boy Laurent Simons heads off to university aged 8 A town in Mexico overthrew their local government. Things couldn’t be going better. Donald Trump's aide held secret talks with Brexiteers over trade deal agreement We Still Have No Idea How To Eliminate 25% of Emissions - Yet we have to eliminate 100% in 20 years to survive We Still Have No Idea How To Eliminate 25% of Emissions - Yet we have to eliminate 100% in 20 years to survive Fentanyl shipment from China worth $1.7 million seized at Philadelphia Port Rudy Giuliani calls for Iran regime change at rally linked to extreme group Trump lawyer speaks at Paris event staged by MeK, once listed as terrorist organisation and widely seen as a personality cult Activists Say The US Has Resumed Late-Night Deportations, Violating An Agreement With Mexico Himmler's daughter worked for post-war German spy agency People With Autoimmune Disorders More Likely To Have Psychosis, Research Shows: 'People with any autoimmune disorder are around 40 percent more likely to develop psychotic disorders such as schizophrenia,' researchers from King's College London concluded. At least six protesters marching against Nicaraguan President Daniel Ortega were shot and wounded, as thousands to the streets across the country. As a march began in Managua, armed men fired on a protesters' barricade at the National Autonomous University of Nicaragua Central Helsingborg Shooting: Full Story &amp; Must-See Details Trump allies push for Iran regime change FRESH MUSIC: Daniwek Ft Xan King – Love You EU migration deal 'agrees that they don’t agree on anything' 12-Year-Old Girl Invents Plastic-Detecting Robot to Save Our Oceans 'I was ordered to leave Russia because of my Fifa T-shirt' Plastic plates and cutlery to be banned from sale under government plans in the UK Donald Trump is thanking Canada for its \"partnership on the global stage\" in a Canada Day message to Governor General Julie Payette. despite the recent tension, Trump tells Payette that the two countries should \"treasure our close bonds.\" Thousands across U.S. join 'Keep Families Together' march to protest family separation Confusion over immigration and crime is roiling European politics All westbound lanes of Highway 401 at Trafalgar Street are closed after a male driver was ejected from a vehicle and killed on Saturday night. The OPP had been referred to as to the scene near Milton simply earlier than 5 p.m. the place they discovered vehicle within the ditch. The driver, the ve",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          58,
          66,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          83,
          88,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          105,
          109,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          194,
          205,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          343,
          357,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          387,
          388,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          399,
          405,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          473,
          487,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          644,
          652,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          755,
          763,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          798,
          803,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          851,
          864,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          875,
          879,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          927,
          932,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          950,
          955,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          972,
          975,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1071,
          1073,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1139,
          1145,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1146,
          1153,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1203,
          1235,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1426,
          1447,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1521,
          1534,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1626,
          1633,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1793,
          1798,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1815,
          1819,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1847,
          1854,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1858,
          1866,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1878,
          1880,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1939,
          1950,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2031,
          2037,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2052,
          2056,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2146,
          2148,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2149,
          2161,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2174,
          2180,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2228,
          2238,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2267,
          2280,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2310,
          2315,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2322,
          2329,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2405,
          2409,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2668,
          2676,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2688,
          2691,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2734,
          2740,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "May 03, 2018 Hollywood isn’t simply churning out crummy remakes of nice movies anymore — now it’s doing terrible remakes of mediocre movies. For proof, see “Overboard.” Or, moderately, don’t. Who wants an up to date model of that weird Goldie Hawn-Kurt Russell comedy through which a wealthy girl tumbles off h Iran's foreign minister: US has ‘consistently violated’ Iran nuclear agreement Rihanna covers the June 2018 problem of Vogue journal, and in her cowl story, she reveals a variety of issues, however essentially the most notable revelation must be the truth that she and Drake are now not mates. In her interview, RiRi opened up about Drake’s tremendous awkward VMA Vanguard awa U.S. soldiers are secretly fighting Saudi Arabia's war in Yemen, report says Canadian MP Bob Saroya took trip to China paid for by Chinese Communist Party 2017 Best Black Friday and Cyber Monday Mattress Deals on Memory … NBC, ABC Say Trump Lawyer Michael Cohen Was Not Wiretapped, Issue Corrections | HuffPost South Korean janitor may keep gold bars found in airport trash can Last chance: UN warns Cambodia over failing democracy 3 Quick Ways to Get into Your Customer’s Head for your Marketing Video – Fab Mini-Tutorial Mexico's presidential frontrunner accuses Mexican billionaires of plotting to prevent him from winning the country's July 1 presidential election. López Obrador currently holds a double-digit lead in almost all polls. Watch Crooked Racist Cop Take a Running Start &amp; Kick a Handcuffed and Compliant Black Man Right in The Head (Video) U.S. freezes funding for Syria's \"White Helmets\" Argentina peso crashes 7.8 percent despite second steep central bank interest rate increase in a week The Cutest Choppy Hairstyles You’ll See for 2018 The world’s last male northern white rhino has died on March 19th. Here is why thrifty Chinese search for sky-high price Rhino Horn for medicine. Uruguay's soybean crop forecasted to drop 43% because of devastating drought We Now Have A Working Nuclear Reactor for Other Planets — But No Plan For Its Waste Marketing’s Customer Obsession Imperative | C3 2018 | Ryan Skinner Ex-Trump aide Michael Caputo warns: Mueller Russia probe espousing 'punishment strategy' to deter future Trump-like candidates 11-Year-Old Girl With Autism Wouldn’t Talk In Class, But Sings Like An Angel In Front Of Millions Richard Corkery/NY Each day Information through Getty Photos Do you keep in mind when Princess Diana went to the Met Gala? It was 1996, three years earlier than Anna Wintour took on the position as chair of the now-titled Costume Institute Gala, and the theme was centered on the affect of desi What Makes the Brand Stand Out? UK drones in Syria using controversial 'vacuum' bombs High fruit diet could help women conceive, study suggests",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          236,
          260,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          311,
          315,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          336,
          338,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          367,
          371,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          390,
          397,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          409,
          418,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          430,
          435,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          580,
          585,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          623,
          627,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          644,
          649,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          688,
          692,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          724,
          738,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          746,
          751,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          777,
          787,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          801,
          806,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          819,
          842,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          843,
          847,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          870,
          882,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          910,
          913,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          915,
          918,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          923,
          928,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          936,
          949,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          990,
          998,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1079,
          1081,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1088,
          1096,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1211,
          1217,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1328,
          1334,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1358,
          1371,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1549,
          1553,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1574,
          1579,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1598,
          1607,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1693,
          1699,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1744,
          1748,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1804,
          1814,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1895,
          1902,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2100,
          2107,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2110,
          2122,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2137,
          2151,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2159,
          2166,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2167,
          2173,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2228,
          2233,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2250,
          2261,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2348,
          2363,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2367,
          2375,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2443,
          2448,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2478,
          2482,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2484,
          2495,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2509,
          2521,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2675,
          2677,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2688,
          2693,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "\"The authority must not give a bulk export consent without the prior approval in writing of AWB. I guess they're still waiting for that,\" Alick Osborne from the Grain Exporters Association said.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          92,
          95,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          138,
          151,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          157,
          188,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Maria Dovey from Reptile Rescue Tasmania has these words of advice.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          17,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Despite posting a half-year profit of $4.7 million, the Dairy Farmers Co-operative will push on with a restructure involving the closure of four plants.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          18,
          27,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          52,
          72,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The population of the isolated Western Australian town of Rawlinna is set to boom as people arrive for the annual Nullabor Muster.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          58,
          66,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          107,
          113,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Grain growers in Victoria have formally shown their support for keeping the single desk for wheat exports.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          17,
          25,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jul 08, 2018 Dodgers vs Angeles - MLB, July 8, 2018, at 8:08 pm ET, Live on ESPN, Venue: Angel Stadium of Anaheim. David Davis resigns as Brexit secretary Advocates for improved nutrition for babies have expressed outrage over reports that the Trump administration bullied other governments in an attempt to prevent the passage of an international resolution promoting breastfeeding. LIVE: Kildare v Fermanagh and All-Ireland SHC preliminary quarter-finals Croatia`s player Vida warned over pro-Ukraine comments Dodgers vs Angeles - MLB, July 8, 2018, at 8:08 pm ET, Live on ESPN, Venue: Angel Stadium of Anaheim. British Brexit Secretary David Davis resigns over EU exit plan: source Terrorist Attack In Saudi Arabia Thwarted With 2 Terrorists Killed and 1 In Custody Brexit Secretary David Davis resigns over EU exit plan - source British Brexit Secretary David Davis resigns over EU exit plan: source UK media: Most senior Brexit official quits government Tunisia vows to avenge 6 guard troops killed near border A mysterious surge in emissions of an illegal ozone-destroying chemical has been tracked down to plastic foam manufacturers in China, according to an on-the-ground investigation published on Monday. The chemical, trichlorofluoromethane or CFC-11, has been banned around the world since 2010 Dodgers vs Angeles - MLB, July 8, 2018, at 8:08 pm ET, Live on ESPN, Venue: Angel Stadium of Anaheim. New Protests In Southern Iran Over Water Shortages Anti-Trump Balloon Upstaged by Anti-Sadiq Khan Balloon Le Pen calls for ‘peaceful yet militant’ protest as judges freeze €2mn of subsidies to her party Thai cave rescue: Weakest boys extracted first What’s on TV Sunday: ‘Sharp Objects’ and ‘Snowden’ Philippines president Duterte says he will quit if someone can prove God exists ‘It was blackmail’: US ‘bullied other countries to stop WHO promoting breastfeeding’ ‘It was blackmail’: US ‘bullied other countries to stop WHO promoting breastfeeding’ Dodgers vs Angeles - MLB, July 8, 2018, at 8:08 pm ET, Live on ESPN, Venue: Angel Stadium of Anaheim. U.K. woman dies after exposure to Novichok, the same nerve agent used in Skripal attack UK Brexit secretary resigns amid split in government over May's proposal",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          24,
          31,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          39,
          51,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          76,
          80,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          106,
          113,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          115,
          126,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          240,
          264,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          390,
          397,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          400,
          409,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          414,
          429,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          474,
          478,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          512,
          519,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          523,
          530,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          533,
          536,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          538,
          550,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          575,
          579,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          605,
          612,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          639,
          650,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          664,
          666,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          705,
          717,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          786,
          797,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          811,
          813,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          858,
          869,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          883,
          885,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          904,
          906,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          959,
          966,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1143,
          1148,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1207,
          1213,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1302,
          1306,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1307,
          1314,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1318,
          1325,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1328,
          1331,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1333,
          1345,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1370,
          1374,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1491,
          1506,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1515,
          1521,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1672,
          1678,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1710,
          1721,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1732,
          1739,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1810,
          1812,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1846,
          1849,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1895,
          1897,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1931,
          1934,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1960,
          1978,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1981,
          1984,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1986,
          1998,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2023,
          2027,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2053,
          2060,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2062,
          2066,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2135,
          2142,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2150,
          2152,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2208,
          2211,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Iraq market",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Fresh roadkill sought for WA snake study",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          26,
          28,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "May 01, 2018 North Korea to open its sky, South Korean media reports. The Mueller probe ain't ending anytime soon BRAND NEW: 2018 – Renault Alpine A110 – Start-UP &amp; Loud Sound! The story of the Midwestern innocent let loose in the big city has been a trope in successful comedies from “Tales of the City” (1993) to “Girls” (2012). “Sweetbitter,” a new, six-episode series on Starz, takes another naif, doe-eyed Tess (Ella Purnell), and sets her loose in the New York City of Mattis tempers optimistic outlook on Afghanistan after twin bombings Facebook is taking on Tinder with new dating features OECD chief says Greece deserves debt relief after 'enormous' reform effort Facebook to launch dating service U.N. could help Myanmar gather evidence of crimes against Rohingya: British envoy PTSD veterans 'cured' with ecstasy treatment in weeks, say scientists May Day protesters demand better rights for workers China’s Social Credit System Punishes Low-Score Parents by Limiting What Schools Their Children Attend Paris police arrest 200 in May Day riots Trump Could Be Charged With Conspiracy To Defraud The United States The best shampoo to regrow hair A specially formulated DHT blocker shampoo to reverse hair loss and regrow thick hair No hair treatment shampoo is stronger Iran's Nuclear Threat Jean 'Binta' Breeze Performance At Dis Poem: Wordz &amp; Agro Festival 2018 Migrant says he ‘accidentally’ raped a Belgian woman: “I wasn’t myself that day” My Email Newsletter of Curated Marketing Content Mueller asks for 2 more months before Flynn sentencing, suggesting continued cooperation Mueller asks for 2 more months before Flynn sentencing Canada to tack a carbon price of at least 11 cents a liter on gasoline Kanye West: 'The class war is one of the reasons why Trump won' Michael Stewart/WireImage Kylie Jenner simply revealed a new option to obtain the right liner with little effort and time. Though the Preserving Up With the Kardashians star’s Snapchat and Instagram makes it clear that she’s obsessive about magnificence, the brand new mother would not all th For first time health ministry will regulate descriptions on medical institutions’ websites as “advertisements” to protect patients from unscrupulous operators..prohibit misleading claims “100 percent safe surgery”..ban patients’ testimonies &amp; touting medical treatments that use unapproved drugs.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          24,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          74,
          81,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          125,
          129,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          132,
          139,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          310,
          314,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          328,
          332,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          379,
          384,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          415,
          419,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          421,
          433,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          458,
          475,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          479,
          485,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          516,
          527,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          548,
          556,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          570,
          576,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          602,
          606,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          618,
          624,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          677,
          685,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          711,
          715,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          727,
          734,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          841,
          846,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          863,
          870,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          915,
          920,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1018,
          1023,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1045,
          1052,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1059,
          1064,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1109,
          1126,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1283,
          1287,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1305,
          1316,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1511,
          1518,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1528,
          1541,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1549,
          1554,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1600,
          1607,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1617,
          1630,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1638,
          1643,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1655,
          1661,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1726,
          1736,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1779,
          1784,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1790,
          1805,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1816,
          1828,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1966,
          1974,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1979,
          1988,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Farmers are warning the Federal Government to take its time negotiating a free trade deal with China after a push by Chinese Premier Wen Jiabao to accelerate talks.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          20,
          42,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          95,
          100,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          133,
          143,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jun 01, 2018 Paris 'Spider-Man' joins fire brigade after citizenship fast-tracked African finance leaders to debate China's yuan as a reserve currency Israeli Army Kills Palestinian Nurse In Gaza Border Protest U.S. Vetoes U.N. Resolution on Gaza, Fails to Win Second Vote on its Own Measure 'Netanyahu asked Shin Bet head to listen to phones of then-IDF, Mossad chiefs' The U.S. is trying to find a discreet way to pay for Kim Jong Un’s hotel during the summit Belgians' anger grows over status of parents of girl killed by police BDS in United States discovered funding terrorist organizations Arnold Schwarzenegger roasts Trump on coal: I look forward to protections for Blockbuster Schwarzenegger mocks Trump on coal bailout: Protect pagers, Blockbuster too Malyasia's Anwar backs Mahathir’s review of Chinese deals Trump says Singapore talks with Kim Jong-un are back on Malaysian finance chief: ties with China, Singapore not derailed by loss of infrastructure projects Many Visa cards in Europe aren’t working due to a network outage Nicaragua protests: More than 100 killed since April Embattled Chinese Telecom Giant ZTE Hired Trump Campaign Veteran UN reaches deal with Myanmar to repatriate Rohingya refugees Malaysian Finance Ministerhas said the government’s decision this week to scrap a high-speed rail project between Kuala Lumpur and Singapore came down to the prohibitively high cost burden his country would be saddled with to maintain the 350km link in the longer term Myanmar and U.N. Agree to Aim for Repatriation of Rohingya Chinese tourism boom blamed as Thai beach from Leonardo DiCaprio film 'The Beach' closes UN knew of sex-for-food scandal at top charities Anker Soundcore Vortex review: Huge value, low price Amnesty International says Illegal demolition and forcible transfer of Palestinian Bedouin village amounts to war crime Is that... Valerie Jarrett ? Taiwan to loan ally Haiti $150 million amid China onslaught",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          18,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          116,
          121,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          191,
          195,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          211,
          215,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          223,
          227,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          242,
          246,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          293,
          302,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          309,
          317,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          351,
          354,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          356,
          362,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          375,
          379,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          424,
          437,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          532,
          535,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          539,
          552,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          596,
          617,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          625,
          630,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          674,
          685,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          686,
          700,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          707,
          712,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          746,
          757,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          762,
          770,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          773,
          778,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          785,
          793,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          820,
          825,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          831,
          840,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          852,
          863,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          911,
          916,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          918,
          927,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          981,
          985,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          995,
          1001,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1041,
          1050,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1088,
          1093,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1126,
          1129,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1136,
          1141,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1159,
          1161,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1180,
          1187,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1281,
          1290,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1334,
          1346,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1351,
          1360,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1489,
          1496,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1501,
          1505,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1595,
          1612,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1637,
          1639,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1686,
          1691,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1739,
          1760,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1870,
          1885,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1888,
          1894,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1908,
          1913,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1932,
          1937,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A 3 per cent fall in the US exchange this week should have led to higher wool prices in Australia.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          25,
          27,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          37,
          46,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          88,
          97,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Austfish has been placed in receivership with higher operating costs, cheaper imports and season limits believed to be responsible.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          90,
          96,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Increased production in Australia and strong global competition will keep grain prices low.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          24,
          33,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Queensland Dairyfarmers Organisation (QDO) has set up its own cyclone relief fund to provide help to farmers affected by cyclone Larry.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          42,
          45,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          133,
          138,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "But farmers and other regional businesses say the changes will lead to more jobs in regional Australia and greater flexibility for workers and employers.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          93,
          102,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Chair of the study, Queensland Nationals president, Bruce Scott says there needs to be greater debate on community attitudes to recycled water.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          20,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          52,
          63,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "\"But however, we all got together and sure enough I did manage to get them all together and they went off on Tuesday night and they will be the bouquets today and tomorrow.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          153,
          158,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          163,
          171,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Category two Cyclone Hubert is expected to cross the Pilbara coast late tonight.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          53,
          60,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "It is carried by silver leaf whitefly and quarantine measures are expected to be announced this week.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          91,
          100,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "John Macleod from Roberts Limited says the company bid when the board was first privatised.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          18,
          33,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Global oil prices continue to climb to record heights as Australia's grain growers prepare for this year's planting season.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          57,
          66,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          95,
          106,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Aug 10, 2018 China is tracking Muslims embarking on the annual Hajj pilgrimage in what experts say is likely part of widespread government surveillance Second Ancient Egyptian Sphinx Discovered in Luxor Sky News: Indian MP dresses as Adolf Hitler in protest against PM Narendra Modi Tesla Inc and Chief Executive Elon Musk were sued on Friday by an investor who said they committed securities fraud in a scheme to “completely decimate” short-sellers that included Musk’s proposal to take the electric car company private. China’s business and energy ties with Iran do not harm the interests of any other country, the country’s Foreign Ministry said, after U.S. President Donald Trump said companies doing business with Iran would be barred from the United States. Iran tested anti-ship missile in Strait of Hormuz, say US officials Romania's expats return home for anti-government protest Put on Your Dancing Shoes! Justin Timberlake Wrote a Book 200+ injured in violent clashes, tear gas used, Around 100,000 at Diaspora protest in Bucharest; More protests erupt in large Romanian cities China bans Winnie the Pooh film after comparisons to President Xi | World news Three paedophiles shot and hanged for rape of boy in Yemen Once ‘No Longer a Nuclear Threat,’ North Korea Now in Standoff With U.S. Ottawa mosque loses charity status for promoting ‘hate and intolerance’ It is shaping as much as be one other lovely weekend in Toronto, however metropolis workers have warned Torontonians to remain away from the water at 5 of the 11 beaches open to the general public. Centre Island Seaside, Ward’s Seaside, Cherry Seaside, Sunnyside Seaside and Marie Curtis Park East S Was ist FBA? Was bedeutet fulfillment by Amazon? The Marines didn’t think women belonged in combat. She’s proving them wrong Betty White, nonetheless going robust at 96, is the topic of “Betty White: First Girl of Tv,” a new documentary airing Aug. 21 on PBS (eight p.m.) Filmed over a five-year interval by Steven J. Boettcher and Michael J. Trinklein, the movie takes a deep dive into White’s 80-year show-business profe Afghan forces launched a clearing operation Friday, searching for Taliban fighters following a major assault on the southeastern city of Ghazni, after US air strikes targeted insurgents trying to overrun the city In Bucharest Piata Victoriei protests, two Geandarmes were extracted from violent mob by protesters (00:50-02:50) Bulk SMS Service for Faridabad – All That You Need to Know! Jury awards $289 million in damages after man says he got terminal cancer from Monsanto's Roundup Iran tests ballistic missile for first time this year: report Arrested in Dubai for drink 1 glass of wine on a plane. Sakshi Malik and Satyawart Kadian: Floored on the mat Censored from the front page of reddit with 27,000 net upvotes; \"Man arrested at New Mexico compound is son of imam with possible link to 1993 World Trade Center bombing.\"",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          18,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          56,
          62,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          197,
          202,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          234,
          246,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          269,
          282,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          283,
          292,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          313,
          322,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          336,
          342,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          464,
          468,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          522,
          527,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          560,
          564,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          627,
          643,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          656,
          660,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          671,
          683,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          719,
          723,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          745,
          762,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          764,
          768,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          797,
          813,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          819,
          821,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          832,
          839,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          916,
          933,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1033,
          1042,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1089,
          1094,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1100,
          1115,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1152,
          1154,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1221,
          1226,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1262,
          1273,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1295,
          1299,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1300,
          1306,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1417,
          1424,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1428,
          1435,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1593,
          1607,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1609,
          1623,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1625,
          1642,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1713,
          1719,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1725,
          1732,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1797,
          1808,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1838,
          1840,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1916,
          1923,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1927,
          1930,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1958,
          1967,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1980,
          1999,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2004,
          2024,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2059,
          2064,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2067,
          2074,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2139,
          2145,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2161,
          2168,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2232,
          2238,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2246,
          2248,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2311,
          2320,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2321,
          2336,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2351,
          2361,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2443,
          2452,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2561,
          2569,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2580,
          2584,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2624,
          2633,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2654,
          2659,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2698,
          2710,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2715,
          2731,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2784,
          2790,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2833,
          2843,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2890,
          2894,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jul 01, 2018 The liftoff of James Webb, the successor to the agency’s iconic Hubble Space Telescope, has been pushed back from May 2020 to March 2021, NASA officials announced today Police used tear gas, dogs and batons to push back crowds celebrating Istanbul's 16th Pride March on Sunday. The people, carrying rainbow flags and banners, had been marching down the city's central Istiklal shopping street as part of the pride celebrations. India to Adopt New Nuclear-Capable ICBM as 'Strategic Deterrent' - Reports Transwoman wins Miss Universe Spain 2018 Bolton: U.S. Has Plan to Dismantle North Korea's Nukes in a Year China fails to lure foreign funds as trade dispute hits stocks, yuan The UN says 18.5 million Americans are in ‘extreme poverty;’ Trump’s team says just 250,000 are US and North Korean officials met Sunday to discuss implementing agreement between countries Brexit's biggest campaign donor 'investigated by National Crime Agency over links to Russia' What Does Trumps Space Force Mean For The Secret Space Force? What’s Going On In Space? – Collective Evolution North Korea Expands Key Missile-Manufacturing Plant Trump, Putin Will Discuss Russian Election Meddling Ministers 'rehearse for Queen's death for first time in secret exercise' Survivors of deadly tour boat explosion airlifted to US Axios has obtained a leaked draft of a Trump administration bill — ordered by the president himself — that would declare America’s abandonment of fundamental World Trade Organization rules. ANSI B16.9 ASTM A403 WP321 90 Degree Elbow Short Radius DN32 SCH40S - Yaang Celebrity Sparks Controversy After Saying She’s Going To Raise A Vegan Child Without Vaccinations – Collective Evolution Paris helicopter prison break for “Hollywood style” gangster Russian hackers probe, could affect U.S. food systems, says AU professor 1 big thing: Exclusive — Leaked Trump bill to blow up the WTO ​ Pakistan hands over list of 471 Indian prisoners: foreign ministry Kim Kardashian West and Kris Jenner make one gorgeous group! The mother-daughter duo coordinated in black-and-white ensembles on Saturday throughout an look on the KKW Beauty pop-up store in Century Metropolis, Calif. Kim’s make-up artist Mario Dedivanovic and hairstylist Chris Appleton have bee Anti Trump populist poised to clinch Mexican Presidency US Reaffirms Opposition to Russian Gas Pipeline Projects Ahead of Trump-Putin Summit German Interior Minister Horst Seehofer offered his resignation to party colleagues late on Sunday, party officials said, escalating a row over migration with Chancellor Angela Merkel that threatens her fragile government.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          28,
          38,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          127,
          135,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          139,
          149,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          151,
          155,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          176,
          181,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          252,
          260,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          283,
          289,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          381,
          389,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          441,
          446,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          552,
          556,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          557,
          563,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          565,
          569,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          592,
          605,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          615,
          621,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          622,
          627,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          695,
          697,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          752,
          757,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          787,
          789,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          821,
          827,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          880,
          886,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          929,
          950,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          965,
          971,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1084,
          1095,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1136,
          1141,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1143,
          1148,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1314,
          1316,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1317,
          1322,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1356,
          1361,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1438,
          1445,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1475,
          1499,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1577,
          1582,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1683,
          1703,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1704,
          1709,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1739,
          1748,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1801,
          1805,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1825,
          1827,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1870,
          1875,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1896,
          1899,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1902,
          1910,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1969,
          1988,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1993,
          2004,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2098,
          2106,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2133,
          2143,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2160,
          2178,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2187,
          2190,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2208,
          2225,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2242,
          2256,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2266,
          2276,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2322,
          2324,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2388,
          2393,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2432,
          2446,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2577,
          2590,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "In the steep uplands of Liquica overlooking the capital of Dili, some maize farmers have recorded yields of up to three tonnes per hectare.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          24,
          31,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          59,
          63,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Senior counsel assisting the inquiry John Agius told a packed hearing room, the Prime Minister will supply by 4pm tomorrow his confidential statement documenting when he first learned of irregular payments by AWB to the Iraqi regime.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          37,
          47,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          209,
          212,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Grains Council says Australian Wheat Associates would be modelled on industry bodies for the meat and dairy sectors.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          24,
          51,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "But the trials have now been dumped, with AQIS warning the biological agent poses a biosecurity risk and could carry mad cow disease.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          42,
          46,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Agriculture Minister Peter McGauran has set a deadline of 2008 to implement the scheme, which he says will improve the environment and lift farm productivity.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          35,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          58,
          62,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Aug 23, 2019 Trump raises tariffs on Chinese goods after stocks tumble Donald Trump orders US companies to 'start looking for alternatives' to China - Donald Trump's America China People's Daily's weibo made racist poster about Hong Kong Way: \"Do not hold the black hand\" Tanzania detains Watetezi TV journalist over investigation of police Clashes at Kashmir protest after Friday prayers - BBC That is actually what desires are manufactured from! Hilary Duff is returning as Lizzie McGuire in a sequel of the favored Disney Channel sequence, set to stream on Disney+. This time, Lizzie is a 30 year-old millennial navigating life in New York Metropolis, and the present’s unique creator Te EU countries agree to share out Ocean Viking migrants US companies 'hereby ordered' in a Tweet by President Trump to exit China manufacturing Woman arrested at anti-government protest accuses Hong Kong police of humiliating and unnecessary strip search Accountant tells how a UK charity she worked with refused to let her handle money because Nigerians are known for fraud Cleveland Browns vs Tampa Bay Buccaneers - August 23, 2019 France threatens to block trade over Amazon fires Brazil’s Rainforest Fires Prompt Alarm and Anger in Europe Trump offers Brazil help with Amazon fires Unrest in Hong Kong fuels speculation of spike in 're-return migration' to Canada China hopes Donald Trump ‘honours’ earlier hands-off stance on Hong Kong despite latest US trade war link Russia rocket accident likely had two explosions, Norway monitor says Trump Offers Brazil Help on Amazon After Macron Faulted Brazil Two victims of mysterious Russian missile blast died of radiation sickness, report says Lead pollution in Zambia town a public health 'emergency': Human Rights Watch China-based firms look to obscure tariff loophole to dodge trade war, but US customs is cracking down Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez and Greta Thunberg want everyone to fly less to fight climate change. Germany and Sweden are already embracing the 'flight shame' movement Immigration to Britain hits five-year low ahead of Brexit Gaza banks to dole out Qatari cash to 100,000 families starting Sunday Mexico Judge Approves Recreational Cocaine Use, Citing 'Personal and Spiritual' Benefits",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          18,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          71,
          83,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          91,
          93,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          143,
          148,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          151,
          165,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          166,
          179,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          180,
          194,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          228,
          237,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          272,
          280,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          289,
          297,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          352,
          359,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          374,
          380,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          391,
          394,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          448,
          459,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          476,
          490,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          518,
          532,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          560,
          567,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          580,
          586,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          592,
          603,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          634,
          642,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          643,
          653,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          691,
          693,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          745,
          747,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          799,
          804,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          813,
          818,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          883,
          892,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          967,
          969,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1064,
          1080,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1084,
          1104,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1107,
          1122,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1123,
          1129,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1160,
          1166,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1173,
          1179,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1225,
          1231,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1232,
          1237,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1245,
          1251,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1262,
          1268,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1285,
          1294,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1350,
          1356,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1357,
          1362,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1369,
          1381,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1420,
          1429,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1445,
          1447,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1463,
          1469,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1513,
          1519,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1533,
          1538,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1546,
          1552,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1561,
          1567,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1574,
          1580,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1589,
          1595,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1702,
          1708,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1743,
          1761,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1762,
          1767,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1836,
          1838,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1864,
          1888,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1893,
          1907,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1959,
          1966,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1971,
          1977,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2043,
          2050,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2056,
          2065,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2086,
          2090,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2150,
          2156,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2157,
          2163,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Oct 06, 2018 Nicola Adams beats Mexican Isabel Millan to close in on world title bout The disunited states: US divides grow deeper over Kavanaugh appointment Cameroon set for Sunday vote as Paul Biya seeks seventh term In Indonesia, parents wait for children’s bodies to be pulled from church wreckage Syfy’s ‘Nightflyers’ Takes Psychological Horror into House Anger vs. elation: Parties scrap for Kavanaugh edge in midterms Turkish authorities believe that prominent Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi, who disappeared four days ago after entering Saudi Arabia’s consulate in Istanbul, was killed inside the consulate, two Turkish sources said on Saturday. Brett Kavanaugh Has Been Confirmed To The Supreme Court Cameroon set for Sunday vote as Paul Biya seeks seventh term A Third Of The Men On The Supreme Court Now Face Sexual Misconduct Accusations Voters strongly back ‘trustworthy’ May as Johnson’s leadership bid backfires - Poll taken after party conference season puts prime minister well ahead of her main challenger Last orders as Tokyo’s famed Tsukiji fish market closes Turkey has concluded that a missing Saudi journalist was murdered by a special hit squad inside Saudi Arabia's consulate in Istanbul. The prominent commentator was last seen entering the diplomatic mission. Turkish authorities believe that prominent Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi, who disappeared four days ago after entering Saudi Arabia’s consulate in Istanbul, was killed inside the consulate, two Turkish sources said on Saturday. This airdrop platform is so unique and trusted in cryptosystem. Register and get your rewards. Medical Cannabis to Be Studied in Nursing Homes Texas Is Back MSF asked to leave Nauru. Turkey concludes Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi killed by ‘murder’ team, sources say California’s efforts to get more women on company boards are toothless, patronising and quite possibly illegal 259 people have died taking selfies since 2011 Saudi journalist 'killed inside consulate' – Turkish sources of Banksy Art Piece That Auto shreds after sell - Screen record of orig Banksy video deleted from instagram My girlfriend told me she was suicidal. Here’s what happened next – ABC Life You Can Now Get A Fry Up Inside A Loaf Of Bread",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          25,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          40,
          53,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          86,
          107,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          108,
          110,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          136,
          145,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          158,
          166,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          175,
          181,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          190,
          199,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          222,
          231,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          302,
          306,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          398,
          407,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          485,
          500,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          518,
          531,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          547,
          561,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          575,
          583,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          646,
          654,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          656,
          671,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          694,
          711,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          712,
          720,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          729,
          735,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          744,
          753,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          795,
          812,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          887,
          890,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          894,
          901,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1041,
          1046,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1055,
          1062,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1082,
          1088,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1178,
          1192,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1206,
          1214,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1349,
          1364,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1382,
          1395,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1411,
          1425,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1439,
          1447,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1510,
          1518,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1663,
          1668,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1677,
          1680,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1696,
          1701,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1703,
          1709,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1737,
          1752,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1790,
          1800,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1943,
          1947,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2081,
          2087,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2107,
          2116,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2185,
          2193,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Grower Bruce Munro says it was a nervous wait on Thursday evening.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          7,
          18,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          49,
          57,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "\"So we know our own crazy ewes they are probably rearing 20 to 30 per cent less lambs and that's mirrored by some very good research in Western Australia.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          136,
          153,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Oct 12, 2018 Intersectional Feminism Broke Her Wada: Anti-doping campaigner Beckie Scott says officials tried ‘to bully’ her United States or China as world leader? Asians overwhelmingly prefer the US, Pew study finds - Poll shows that Beijing’s record on human rights affects opinions about Chinese leadership, with Asians in Japan, South Korea, the Philippines, Indonesia and Australia having a dimmer view of the country Canada gives $50-million to UN Palestinian refugee agency that U.S. calls flawed Cases of polio-like illness appear to be on the rise across the U.S. Severe rights abusers get seats on UN Human Rights Council - Some of the world's worst rights abusers already have seats on the UN Human Rights Council. The Philippines and Eritrea have been controversially elected to join the likes of Saudi Arabia and Egypt. After the unfortunate incident, a sudden US decision on the most expensive fighter — Steemit Key EU lawmaker's plan to rein in online marketplaces a threat to Amazon ‘I love him so much I can hardly explain it’: Evangelical leaders praise Trump after pastor’s release The chair of the World Anti-Doping Agency's (Wada) Athlete Committee says some of the organisation's most senior officials tried to \"bully\" her over her opposition to Russian reinstatement. UK drawing up list of potential Saudi sanctions targets after disappearance of journalist Jamal Khashoggi - List could be used if UK decides to invoke ‘Magnitsky amendment’, which allows Britain to impose sanctions on foreign officials accused of human rights violations British Masters: Eddie Pepperell pulls clear as Tommy Fleetwood slips back British Masters: Eddie Pepperell pulls clear as Tommy Fleetwood slips back Big tobacco’s smoke and mirrors act Beto O’Rourke Fundraising Triples Ted Cruz’s In Texas Senate Race Kehlani Is Pregnant And Glowing — See Her Bump-Baring Reveal British Masters: Eddie Pepperell pulls clear as Tommy Fleetwood slips back France to build a fence along its border with Belgium to prevent African Swine Fever from spreading Understanding ‘Moneyland’ — the lawless offshore world of the super-rich Big tobacco’s smoke and mirrors act How Much Could Jamal Khashoggi’s Apple Watch Tell Us About His Disappearance? Couple Divorces After Husband Saw Wife Cheating on Google Street View Pat Riley Says He Didn’t Call Tom Thibodeau ‘Motherf–ker’ in Jimmy Butler Talks ask? because he can! Bipartisan Hill anger with Saudis flares after Khashoggi",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          36,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          76,
          88,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          125,
          138,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          142,
          147,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          198,
          200,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          202,
          205,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          236,
          243,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          327,
          332,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          334,
          345,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          347,
          362,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          364,
          373,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          378,
          387,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          424,
          430,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          452,
          454,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          487,
          491,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          569,
          573,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          609,
          632,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          698,
          725,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          731,
          742,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          747,
          754,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          810,
          822,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          827,
          832,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          875,
          877,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          919,
          926,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          931,
          933,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1073,
          1078,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1115,
          1145,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1147,
          1151,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1292,
          1294,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1382,
          1397,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1422,
          1424,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1444,
          1453,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1479,
          1486,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1580,
          1595,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1611,
          1626,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1655,
          1670,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1686,
          1701,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1749,
          1762,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1783,
          1793,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1797,
          1802,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1815,
          1822,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1893,
          1908,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1924,
          1939,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1951,
          1957,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1997,
          2004,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2175,
          2192,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2308,
          2317,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2338,
          2351,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2369,
          2381,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2420,
          2424,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2456,
          2465,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Bureau of Meteorology is review its HF radio marine weather service.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "With temperatures soaring this summer, particularly in southern Australia, snakes are on the move.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          26,
          37,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          64,
          73,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A Federal Court Judge has reserved his decision on whether to make AWB's so-called apology document public.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          2,
          15,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          67,
          70,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Apr 28, 2019 Using Apple Pay At Drive-Thrus Could Get You Six Points And £200 Fine Canadian among oil workers kidnapped by gunmen in Nigeria | CBC News Iran's Worsening Economic Situations Sees Latest Inflation Figures Topping 50% - Food Prices Jumping to 85% Watch Rockets’ Mike D’Antoni Say Refs Admitted They Missed 4 Fouls vs. Warriors قاضی پور: قواعد واگذاری در مورد نیشکر هفت تپه رعایت نشده است End the Slaughter of Rare Antelopes for Luxury Scarves Australian airport chaos, thousands stuck in queues after IT problem Spain’s ruling socialists won the most votes but fell short of a majority in Sunday’s snap general election, a contest marked by the breakthrough of the far-right Vox party and a disastrous performance by the country’s traditional conservative party. Richard Lugar, Former U.S. Senator And Foreign Policy Powerhouse, Dies At 87 سویا با تساوی صدر جدول را به بارسلونا واگذار کرد Clic no link, veja o vídeo, deixe o like, subscreva no canal, compartilhe no Facebook e aqui no reddit. BGM   Kim Kardashian’s chill baby shower included CBD and meditation: ‘Everyone have a puff’ One week after deadly Easter attacks, faith leaders in Sri Lanka fear reprisals — but vow to unite country | CBC News Australian airport chaos, thousands stuck in queues after IT problem Chilling Twitter feed from Ex Muslim: \"I don't want to die, please help\" Over 1,000 Migrants ESCAPE Detention Center, Hundreds Board Train Headed For US Wow!!! Adorable Mom, Victoria Is Very Angry and Fighting , Biting Her Baby Updated version for Skygrid Download free Shooting kills college football player, injures Giants’ pick Belgium: State Security Says Number of ‘Extremist’ Imams Doubled in Last Two Years [Why are Europeans allowing terrorists to stay? Deport the terrorists and keep freedom loving legal immigrants who assimilate and learn the language.] Adorable Oldest Boss, Mr Tor Is Looking For Food Eating in The River https://apkfilesbucket.blogspot.com/2019/04/download-skygrid-apk-updated-version-105.html NFL Draft 2019 Results: Reviewing This Year’s Best Value Picks Russia’s Navy is Falling Behind the U.S. Navy in Combat Power: Report",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          133,
          140,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          143,
          151,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          152,
          156,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          266,
          273,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          275,
          288,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          331,
          339,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          525,
          530,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          602,
          608,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          688,
          691,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          776,
          789,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          798,
          802,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          815,
          840,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          850,
          852,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1006,
          1009,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1012,
          1028,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1099,
          1107,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1121,
          1127,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1154,
          1163,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1208,
          1216,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1436,
          1438,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1460,
          1468,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1534,
          1541,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1604,
          1610,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1617,
          1624,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1685,
          1699,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          1876,
          1879,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          2049,
          2053,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2073,
          2079,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2082,
          2086,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          2105,
          2118,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Cattle and grain producer Karen Coe hopes it will change city people's perceptions of agriculture.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          26,
          35,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Grains industry analysts say Australia could lose a deal to supply hundreds of tonnes of wheat to Iraq, unless it moves quickly to seal the contract.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          29,
          38,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          98,
          102,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "\"John Thevissen from Mincor Resources, because we're based in Western Australia this is our first time in the Northern Territory, we've applied for ground in the Northern Territory to look for base metals copper, lead, zinc and silver.\"",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          1,
          15,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          21,
          37,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          62,
          79,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          106,
          128,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          158,
          180,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jul 22, 2018 GST adjustments: What it means for you How to Knock Off a Assemble A drug to treat malaria - the first such pill to get approval in 60 years - has been given the green light by authorities in the United States. The medicine is specifically for the recurring form of malaria, which makes 8.5 million people ill each year. CDC confirms that McDonald's salads infected people in over 10 states Pompeo to urge Iranians abroad to 'support' anti-regime protests 10 Cities We Need To See Next (And 10 That Should Be Avoided) Mum&amp;#x27;s despairing cry after thugs hurled acid on her three-year-old son on Worcester shopping trip Trump: Obama didn't warn about Russia before election because 'it is all a big hoax' Trump says he 'misspoke' on Russia meddling, hails US intelligence Meet the Reporter Dragged from Trump-Putin Press Conference for Trying to Ask About Nuclear Treaty How To Get More Than 10$ In One Day AI Companies &amp; Cybersecurity:The Race To Build Artificial Intelligence Defenses Mexico's president-elect wrote Trump a plan to reduce migration 'Do not play with lion's tail': Rouhani warns Trump Why did a Russian pay $95M to buy Trump’s Palm Beach mansion? United States legalizes 3D printed Guns! Ecuador is Reportedly Getting Ready to Turn Assange Over to U.K. Authorities As new vaccine scandal grips China, parents say they’ve lost faith in the system | South China Morning Post • r/China NBC/WSJ poll: Public gives Trump thumbs down on Russia, thumbs up on economy Hendrix Cover w/ Amputated Fingers \"Hey Joe\" Lition is The World’s 1st Operational Peer-to-Peer Vitality Investing System ANSI B16.9 ASTM A403 WP304L SMLS 90Deg LR Elbow DN100 Sch40S - Yaang الإمارات تتهم قطر بـ\"تمويل\" نشر \"الإمارات ليكس\" في لبنان Obama Is ‘Responsible’ for Mueller Investigation, Clapper Admits Lin-Manuel Miranda jumped as much as a podium shortly after touchdown in Puerto Rico on Sunday to announce he has helped create a multimillion-dollar fund to spice up the arts within the U.S. territory because it struggles to get better from Hurricane Maria. The Hamilton playwright stated he hope",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          145,
          153,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          205,
          222,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          323,
          332,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          334,
          337,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          352,
          360,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          404,
          410,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          592,
          606,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          614,
          623,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          638,
          643,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          645,
          650,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          669,
          675,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          723,
          728,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          751,
          757,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          774,
          776,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          821,
          826,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1009,
          1015,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1040,
          1045,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1105,
          1112,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1119,
          1124,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1159,
          1164,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1167,
          1177,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1187,
          1200,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1228,
          1235,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1272,
          1279,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1288,
          1292,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1334,
          1339,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1388,
          1412,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1417,
          1422,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1423,
          1426,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1450,
          1455,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1471,
          1477,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1500,
          1507,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          1536,
          1551,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1748,
          1753,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1775,
          1782,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1798,
          1805,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1813,
          1831,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          1886,
          1897,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          1901,
          1907,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          2000,
          2004,
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          2076,
          2084,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Les Blennerhassett from Blenners Transport says without assistance, freight costs could increase by 90 per cent.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          18,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          24,
          42,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Lib MP pushes for NZ apple ban",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          18,
          20,
          "LOC"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
